9026	Phalin maybe worthy of a section depending on the Thai impact while the IDL one should be relegated as it were.	Phalin kann vielleicht einen Abschnitt würdig sein , abhängig von der thailändischen Wirkung , während die IDL sollte wie es sei vernachlässigt werden .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Phalin': [0, 6, 'PERSON'], 'Thai': [50, 54, 'NORP'], 'IDL': [72, 75, 'ORG']}	{'Phalin': [0, 6, 'LOC'], 'thailändischen': [70, 84, 'MISC'], 'IDL': [107, 110, 'MISC']}
2672	especially since their actions were often on behalf of the establishment they worked for.	vor allem , weil ihre Handlungen oft im Namen der Einrichtung waren , für die sie arbeiteten .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
3255	LOL yeah good one mate - have the rest of the day off champ	LOL ja gut ein Freund - haben Sie den Rest des Tages freien Champion	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'one': [14, 17, 'CARDINAL']}	{'LOL': [0, 3, 'MISC']}
4462	She was also being very very mean at the second that I made it	Sie war auch sehr sehr böse in der Sekunde , dass ich es	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'second': [41, 47, 'ORDINAL']}	{}
39	Wow 1 step at a time, we still trying to agree on what should actually be in the table, lol.	Wow 1 Schritt zu einer Zeit , wir versuchen immer noch zu vereinbaren , was eigentlich in der Tabelle sein sollte , lol .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'1': [4, 5, 'CARDINAL']}	{}
9201	Perhaps you are worth less than a cockroach. Ya think???	Vielleicht sind Sie weniger wert als eine Kackerlacke . Ja denke ? ? ?	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
3773	I totally agree. Their website list Italian ice as their product. [URL]	Ich stimme dem vollkommen zu . Ihre Website listet italienisches Eis als ihr Produkt . [ URL ]	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Italian': [36, 43, 'NORP']}	{'italienisches': [51, 64, 'MISC']}
7135	a Steven Colbert is funy and he is only useing he's First Amendment right to Freedom of speech 2 is the Reality article ever going to be unlocked	a Steven Colbert ist lustig und er verwendet nur sein erstes Änderungsantrag Recht auf Meinungsfreiheit 2 ist der Realität Artikel jemals entsperrt werden	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Steven Colbert': [2, 16, 'PERSON'], '2': [95, 96, 'CARDINAL'], 'Reality': [104, 111, 'NORP']}	{'a Steven Colbert': [0, 16, 'PER']}
4935	There might not have been any positive pressure - that was the point of the first commenter.	Es hätte vielleicht keinen positiven Druck gegeben - das war der Punkt des ersten Kommentators .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'first': [76, 81, 'ORDINAL']}	{}
4298	you deleted the article he wrote on my user can you please un-delete it or replace it thankyou ps sorry for deleting one of your pages	Sie haben den Artikel gelöscht , den er auf meinem Benutzer geschrieben hat , können Sie ihn bitte löschen oder ersetzen Danke ps sorry für das Löschen einer Ihrer Seiten	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'ps sorry': [127, 135, 'PER']}
2335	in the first place. Look at the article's history if you don't believe me	an erster Stelle . Schauen Sie sich die Geschichte des Artikels an , wenn Sie mir nicht glauben	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'first': [7, 12, 'ORDINAL']}	{}
5377	Yep, he be the mouthpiece, but his law still stands. Oh, that was friggin' bad.	Ja , er ist der Mundstück , aber sein Gesetz steht immer noch . Oh , das war ziemlich schlimm .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{}
7889	STOP SENDING ME STUPID MESSAGES. I AM FIXING A MISTAKE IN THE ARTICLE.	STOP ME STUPID MESSAGES SSEN . Ich FIXE einen Fehler im Artikel .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'STOP ME STUPID MESSAGES SSEN': [0, 28, 'MISC'], 'FIXE': [35, 39, 'MISC']}
9698	I think they love each other. Isn't it nice to see gay love on Wikipedia !	Ich denke , sie lieben einander . Ist es nicht schön , homosexuelle Liebe auf Wikipedia zu sehen !	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Wikipedia': [63, 72, 'PERSON']}	{'Wikipedia': [78, 87, 'MISC']}
105	Note that the dots of the names other Hong Kong football clubs are also omitted. Thus this page needs to be renamed for consistence.	Beachten Sie , dass die Punkte der Namen anderer Hongkonger Fußballvereine ebenfalls weggelassen werden . Daher muss diese Seite für Konsistenz umbenannt werden .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Hong Kong': [38, 47, 'GPE']}	{'Hongkonger': [49, 59, 'LOC']}
3118	HI everybody i have a question.....i love jake bye	HI alle ich habe eine Frage . . . . . ich liebe Jake bye	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'HI': [0, 2, 'MISC'], 'liebe Jake bye': [42, 56, 'PER']}
4253	back again.. 7 more contributions after the 24 hour block of the IP address.	wieder zurück . 7 weitere Beiträge nach dem 24 Stunden Block der IP - Adresse .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'7': [13, 14, 'CARDINAL'], '24 hour': [44, 51, 'TIME'], 'IP': [65, 67, 'ORG']}	{'IP': [65, 67, 'ORG']}
2728	it is very important. and what is the problem if the page is too long, fellas?	es ist sehr wichtig . und was ist das Problem , wenn die Seite zu lang ist , Freunde ?	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
3398	I've moved your article on Manifest Ltd to your user space for the same reason: .	Ich habe Ihren Artikel über Manifest Ltd aus dem selben Grund in Ihren Benutzerbereich verschoben : .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Manifest Ltd': [27, 39, 'ORG']}	{'Manifest Ltd': [28, 40, 'ORG']}
8999	Ebyabe falsifies information on her repeated bad edit	Ebyabe verfälscht Informationen über ihre wiederholte schlechte Bearbeitung	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Ebyabe': [0, 6, 'ORG']}	{'Ebyabe': [0, 6, 'PER']}
7445	Are you wikistalking me you fucking aspie? Either crawl back to your hugbox or hang yourself.	Sie wikistalking mich du verdammte Spion ? Entweder kriechen Sie zurück zu Ihrem Umarmkasten oder hängen Sie sich selbst .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
7296	Because I need it bad.Real bad. PS: I'm new to Wikipedia editing so I dont quite get what you mean by signing my post using	PS : Ich bin neu auf Wikipedia - Bearbeitung , so dass ich nicht ganz verstehen , was Sie meinen , indem Sie meinen Beitrag unterzeichnen mit	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Wikipedia': [47, 56, 'ORG']}	{'PS': [0, 2, 'ORG'], 'Wikipedia': [21, 30, 'MISC']}
3373	ElinorD is a faggot and a transexual, judging by the name	ElinorD ist ein Homosexuell und transexuell , nach dem Namen zu urteilen	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{}
1913	Does any of this actually have anything to do with improving the article? It reads like a forum topic.	Hat das wirklich etwas mit der Verbesserung des Artikels zu tun ? Es liest wie ein Forum Thema .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
7695	Also you can't deny that Wikipedia has a lot of false information, and that's why people get F's on reports.	Auch können Sie nicht leugnen , dass Wikipedia eine Menge falsche Informationen hat , und das ist , warum Menschen Fs auf Berichten bekommen .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Wikipedia': [25, 34, 'ORG']}	{'Wikipedia': [37, 46, 'MISC']}
2694	Yeah that true. There will always be debate about whether a show or shows has ever jumped or not. It doesn't bother me that the list is gone.	Ja , das ist wahr . Es wird immer eine Debatte darüber geben , ob eine Show oder Show jemals gesprungen ist oder nicht . Es stört mich nicht , dass die Liste weg ist .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
323	I am neutral. Battle sounds more dramatic. In the besieged city of Misrata ... [URL]	Ich bin neutral . Schlacht klingt dramatischer . In der belagerten Stadt Misrata . . . [ URL ]	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Misrata': [67, 74, 'GPE']}	{'Schlacht': [18, 26, 'MISC'], 'Misrata': [73, 80, 'LOC']}
5544	REDIRECT Talk:Elizabeth Jane Caulfeild, Countess of Charlemont	REDIRECT Talk : Elizabeth Jane Caulfeild , Grafin von Charlemont	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Elizabeth Jane Caulfeild': [14, 38, 'PERSON'], 'Charlemont': [52, 62, 'GPE']}	{'REDIRECT Talk': [0, 13, 'MISC'], 'Elizabeth Jane Caulfeild': [16, 40, 'PER'], 'Charlemont': [54, 64, 'MISC']}
6611	During this period the force, in connection with the secondary part of their orders located several sources of water, in the region of .	Während dieser Zeit befanden sich die Streitkräfte im Zusammenhang mit dem zweiten Teil ihrer Befehle mehrere Wasserquellen , in der Region von .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'Zeit': [15, 19, 'MISC'], 'Streitkräfte': [38, 50, 'ORG']}
3128	I will be in contact with IRS and fUCK WIKI over ... FUCK YOU	Ich werde in Kontakt mit IRS und fUCK WIKI über . . . FUCK YOU	[0, 0, 1]	NOT	{'IRS': [26, 29, 'ORG']}	{'IRS': [25, 28, 'ORG'], 'YOU': [59, 62, 'MISC']}
9421	FYI You should check out Vivian Balakrishnan's page. It has been rephrased and defaced by as we speak.	FYI Sie sollten sich die Seite von Vivian Balakrishnan anschauen . Sie wurde in unserer Sprache umgeschrieben und abgeschwächt .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	"{""Vivian Balakrishnan's"": [25, 46, 'PERSON']}"	{'FYI': [0, 3, 'MISC'], 'Vivian Balakrishnan': [35, 54, 'PER']}
4279	Perhaps you should return all the things you maliciously deleted if you ever want to get beyond being a dope ass anthropology student.	Vielleicht sollten Sie alle Dinge zurückgeben , die Sie schädlich gelöscht haben , wenn Sie überhaupt jenseits eines Dope - Arsch - Anthropologie - Student werden wollen .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{}
5792	Hi What did you learn at the Wikipedia workshop today?	Hallo Was haben Sie heute bei der Wikipedia - Werkstatt gelernt ?	[0, 0, 1]	NOT	{'Wikipedia': [29, 38, 'PERSON'], 'today': [48, 53, 'DATE']}	{'Hallo Was': [0, 9, 'PER'], 'Wikipedia': [34, 43, 'MISC']}
2864	being initially search for. and a parting note: GO FUCK YOURSELF	wird zunächst gesucht . und eine Abschiedsnotiz :	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{}
5946	for even the slightest deviation from the party line. Sorry if I put this face on you.	für die geringste Abweichung von der Party - Linie . Entschuldigen Sie mich , wenn ich dieses Gesicht auf Sie setzen .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
8207	References and citations are hard to come by on this topic. There is very little on the Internet about YDE.	Referenzen und Zitate sind schwer zu kommen zu diesem Thema . Es gibt sehr wenig im Internet über YDE .	[0, 1, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Internet': [84, 92, 'MISC'], 'YDE': [98, 101, 'MISC']}
1608	Blutengel produce simply Techno music. There is no Dark Wave sound.	Blutengel produziert einfach Technomusik . Es gibt keinen Dark Wave Sound .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Blutengel': [0, 9, 'GPE']}	{'Blutengel': [0, 9, 'MISC']}
8093	no really, if I'm being blocked for sockpuppetry (see block log), where are my other puppets?}}	Nein wirklich , wenn ich für Sockpuppetry blockiert werde ( siehe Block Log ) , wo sind meine anderen Puppen ? } }	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Sockpuppetry': [29, 41, 'PER'], 'Block Log': [66, 75, 'MISC']}
6504	The first CVS pharmacy in Puerto Rico will open the first half of 2008,can't find the link to the news right now...	Die erste CVS Apotheke in Puerto Rico wird das erste Halbjahr 2008 öffnen , kann nicht den Link zu den Nachrichten jetzt finden . . .	[0, 0, 1]	NOT	"{'first': [4, 9, 'ORDINAL'], 'CVS': [10, 13, 'ORG'], 'Puerto Rico': [26, 37, 'GPE'], 'the first half': [48, 62, 'DATE'], ""2008,can't"": [66, 76, 'CARDINAL']}"	{'CVS': [10, 13, 'ORG'], 'Puerto Rico': [26, 37, 'LOC'], 'Link': [91, 95, 'MISC']}
2973	I've also removed the part about the second 'marriage' because it appears to be a Tudor invention to grant Henry VII's reign legitimacy.	"Ich habe auch den Teil über die zweite "" Verehe "" entfernt , weil es scheint eine Tudor - Erfindung zu sein , um Henry VII ' s Herrschaft Legitimität zu gewähren ."	[0, 1, 1]	ERR	"{'second': [37, 43, 'ORDINAL'], 'Tudor': [82, 87, 'PERSON'], ""Henry VII's"": [107, 118, 'PERSON']}"	"{'Tudor': [82, 87, 'PER'], ""Henry VII ' s Herrschaft"": [113, 137, 'PER']}"
4952	I have removed the bit about being the third biggest sub saharan group as they are north african not sub saharan.	Ich habe das Stück über die drittgrößte Subsahara - Gruppe entfernt , da sie Nordafrika sind , nicht Subsahara .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'third': [39, 44, 'ORDINAL'], 'north african': [83, 96, 'NORP']}	{'Subsahara': [101, 110, 'LOC']}
174	I've prepared your work by linking to the article: [URL] And I see you've prepared the work in the Winter War article. -)))	Ich habe Ihre Arbeit vorbereitet , indem ich auf den Artikel verlinke : [ URL ] Und ich sehe , dass Sie die Arbeit im Winterkrieg Artikel vorbereitet haben . - ) ) )	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'the Winter War': [95, 109, 'EVENT']}	{'Winterkrieg': [118, 129, 'MISC']}
718	your last warning. The next time you vandalize a page, you will be blocked from editing Wikipedia.	Ihre letzte Warnung . Beim nächsten Mal , wenn Sie eine Seite vernichten , werden Sie von der Bearbeitung von Wikipedia gesperrt werden .	[1, 1, 0]	ERR	{'Wikipedia': [88, 97, 'PERSON']}	{'Wikipedia': [110, 119, 'MISC']}
1941	You can rationalize your dishonesty however you want but even wikipedia has an article on the ground zero mosque asswhipe	Sie können Ihre Untreue rationalisieren , aber Sie wollen , aber auch wikipedia hat einen Artikel auf dem Boden Null Moschee asswhipe	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'wikipedia': [62, 71, 'PERSON']}	{'wikipedia': [70, 79, 'MISC']}
1479	since there were no confirmed tornadoes from May 3-6	da es zwischen dem 3 . und 6 . Mai keine bestätigten Tornados gab	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'May 3-6': [45, 52, 'DATE']}	{'Tornados': [53, 61, 'ORG']}
8756	Isn't it galling to see how few people bother with wiki - can you really afford to block the few that do?	Ist es nicht erschreckend zu sehen , wie wenige Leute sich mit Wiki stören - können Sie sich wirklich leisten , die wenigen zu blockieren , die tun ?	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
4568	YES. Harassment! now you have your policy correct ;-) See you later ;-)	JA . Belästigung ! jetzt haben Sie Ihre Politik richtig ; - ) Wir sehen uns später ; - )	[1, 1, 0]	ERR	{}	{'JA': [0, 2, 'ORG']}
2603	That is because most iPod owners do not know about other Portable Music Players. The Transcend Tsonic is more popular than the iPod in many places.	Das ist , weil die meisten iPod - Inhaber nicht über andere tragbare Musik - Player wissen . Die Transcend Tsonic ist populärer als der iPod in vielen Orten .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'iPod': [127, 131, 'ORG'], 'Portable Music Players': [57, 79, 'WORK_OF_ART'], 'The Transcend Tsonic': [81, 101, 'ORG']}	{'iPod': [136, 140, 'MISC'], 'Transcend Tsonic': [97, 113, 'ORG']}
1737	Please don't blank archived AFDs, or anything for that matter.	Bitte füllen Sie nicht archivierte AFDs oder irgendetwas für diese Sache aus .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{}
490	I add some identical informations of foibe massacres: in fact is the same historic context!	Ich füge einige identische Informationen über Folterverbrechen hinzu : Tatsächlich ist der historische Kontext derselbe !	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
6409	contribs]]) ::I can't believe I forgot to sign! (I'm so ashamed...) -P [[Special:Contributions/Aervanath	Ich kann nicht glauben , dass ich mich vergessen habe zu unterzeichnen ! ( Ich bin so schämt . . . ) - P [ [ Special : Contributions / Aervanath	[1, 1, 0]	ERR	{}	{'Special': [109, 116, 'MISC'], 'Aervanath': [135, 144, 'ORG']}
610	Hot]]) and one sattelite service ([[Yes (Israel) 	Hot ] ] ) und einen Satteldienst ( [ [ Ja ( Israel )	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'one': [11, 14, 'CARDINAL'], 'Israel': [41, 47, 'GPE']}	{'Israel': [44, 50, 'LOC']}
9774	Hey ms psychology did you receive the textbook yet?	Hey Frau Psychologie haben Sie das Lehrbuch noch erhalten ?	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'Hey': [0, 3, 'PER']}
3038	Stupid peace of shit stop deleting my stuff asshole go die and fall in a hole go to hell!	Stupid Frieden von Scheiß stop Löschen meine Sachen Arschloch gehen sterben und fallen in ein Loch gehen in die Hölle !	[3, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'Stupid Frieden': [0, 14, 'MISC'], 'Scheiß stop Löschen': [19, 38, 'MISC']}
6568	a Profit Charity Business Organization. Panic selling of peanuts ensue and brought about what is known as the Great Peanut Crisis	eine Profit Charity Business Organisation . Panisches Verkauf von Erdnüssen entspringen und führte zu dem , was als die große Erdnusskrise bekannt ist	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Profit Charity Business Organization': [2, 38, 'ORG'], 'the Great Peanut Crisis': [106, 129, 'FAC']}	{}
5313	Wikipedia doesn't allow that sort of content. Try [URL] if you need help with games.	Wikipedia erlaubt diese Art von Inhalten nicht . Versuchen Sie [ URL ] , wenn Sie Hilfe bei Spielen benötigen .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Wikipedia': [0, 9, 'ORG']}	{'Wikipedia': [0, 9, 'MISC']}
8602	Maybe if you could have kept your goons under control this would not have happened.	Vielleicht , wenn Sie Ihre Gänse unter Kontrolle gehalten hätten , wäre dies nicht geschehen .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{}
5170	Well, he was insulting me and I twisted it around. Check the history	Nun , er beleidigte mich und ich drehte es um . Schaue die Geschichte	[0, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{}
4670	I have done so, but would welcome and accept a revision of it after a response has been given.	Ich habe dies getan , würde aber eine Überarbeitung des Berichts begrüßen und akzeptieren , nachdem eine Antwort gegeben wurde .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
759	The 'Discovery' of 2001 was only designed to get from Earth to Jupiter and return. It doesn't qualify as a 'starship.'	Die ' Entdeckung ' von 2001 wurde nur dazu konzipiert , von der Erde auf Jupiter zu kommen und zurückzukehren . Es ist nicht als ' Starship ' zu qualifizieren .	[0, 1, 1]	ERR	{'Discovery': [5, 14, 'PRODUCT'], '2001': [19, 23, 'DATE'], 'Earth': [54, 59, 'LOC'], 'Jupiter': [63, 70, 'LOC']}	{'Erde': [64, 68, 'LOC'], 'Jupiter': [73, 80, 'LOC'], 'Starship': [131, 139, 'MISC']}
8065	THE PERSONG SITTING TO MY RIGHT IS A STINKY VAGINA FACE	Die Person , die zu meiner Rechten sitzt , ist ein steiniger Vagina - Fuß	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{}
6658	It takes 8 years to get 4,6, and 8 year graduation rates. As such 8 years isn't old in this case.	Es dauert 8 Jahre , um 4 , 6 zu bekommen , und 8 Jahre Graduation Rate . Als solche 8 Jahre ist nicht alt in diesem Fall .	[1, 0, 0]	NOT	{'8 years': [9, 16, 'DATE'], '4,6': [24, 27, 'CARDINAL'], '8 year': [33, 39, 'DATE'], 'As such 8 years': [58, 73, 'DATE']}	{}
7291	Martin Mendez was not an official member of the band until after the recording of My Arms, Your Hearse. Mikael Akerfeldt played the bass on the CD.	Martin Mendez war erst nach der Aufnahme von My Arms , Your Hearse offizielles Mitglied der Band . Mikael Akerfeldt spielte den Bass auf der CD .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Martin Mendez': [0, 13, 'PERSON'], 'My Arms': [82, 89, 'ORG'], 'Mikael Akerfeldt': [104, 120, 'PERSON']}	{'Martin Mendez': [0, 13, 'PER'], 'My Arms': [45, 52, 'ORG'], 'Your Hearse': [55, 66, 'ORG'], 'Mikael Akerfeldt': [99, 115, 'PER'], 'CD': [141, 143, 'MISC']}
2355	what is your deal with kurt Lockwood? why cant you accept that he made the movie trannsexual babysitters 5?	was ist dein Deal mit kurt Lockwood ? warum kannst du nicht akzeptieren , dass er den Film trannsexuell Babysitters 5 gemacht hat ?	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'kurt Lockwood': [23, 36, 'PERSON'], '5': [105, 106, 'CARDINAL']}	{'kurt Lockwood': [22, 35, 'PER'], 'trannsexuell Babysitters 5': [91, 117, 'MISC']}
4330	HAHA. That's great. Yeah, DEFINITELY use that in the article. I didn't realize how crazy people got over this movie! LOL.	HAHA . Das ist toll . Ja , DEFINITELY verwenden Sie das im Artikel . Ich wusste nicht , wie verrückte Leute über diesen Film bekommen ! LOL .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'HAHA': [0, 4, 'ORG'], 'LOL': [136, 139, 'MISC']}
2927	Thanks also for the work on Wyclef Jean. That's a long-term vandalism target in the mode you saw, I have no idea why:(	Danke auch für die Arbeit an Wyclef Jean . Das ist ein langfristiges Vandalismusziel im Modus , den Sie gesehen haben , ich habe keine Ahnung , warum : (	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Wyclef Jean': [28, 39, 'PERSON']}	{'Danke': [0, 5, 'PER'], 'Wyclef Jean': [29, 40, 'PER']}
4403	If it's true in every likely interpretation, then it's a good choice.	Wenn es in jeder wahrscheinlichen Interpretation wahr ist , dann ist es eine gute Wahl .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
7025	response: If you notice I changed it right back. I saved the bad version by accident. Sorry	Antwort : Wenn Sie bemerken , ich habe es wieder geändert . Ich habe die schlechte Version durch Zufall gespeichert . Sorry	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
7378	The Canada article has LESS references than the PRC article.	Der Artikel über Kanada hat weniger Referenzen als der Artikel über die PRC .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Canada': [4, 10, 'GPE'], 'PRC': [48, 51, 'GPE']}	{'Kanada': [17, 23, 'LOC'], 'PRC': [72, 75, 'MISC']}
1851	why does it matter? Do you want to put people off using & editing pages?	Warum ist es wichtig ? Möchten Sie Leute mit der Bearbeitung von Seiten abstellen ?	[1, 1, 0]	ERR	{}	{}
6511	YOU'VE IDENTIFIED ADDITIONAL CITATIONS, INCORPORATE THEM. REVISE THE ARTICLE SO IT ISN'T A BLATANT COPYVIO PROBLEM. SIMPLE.	Sie haben zusätzliche Anmerkungen identifiziert , unverantwortliche . Überprüfen Sie den Artikel , damit es kein böses COPYVIO - Problem ist . Einfach .	[1, 1, 0]	ERR	"{""YOU'VE"": [0, 6, 'PERSON'], 'COPYVIO': [99, 106, 'ORG']}"	{'COPYVIO': [119, 126, 'ORG'], 'Einfach': [143, 150, 'MISC']}
2500	And I have a question on the Reference Desk that I need to ask.}}	Und ich habe eine Frage auf dem Referenztisch , die ich stellen muss . } }	[1, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Referenztisch': [32, 45, 'LOC']}
8907	I shall leave a attack message on whoever i chose kty bye	Ich werde eine Angriffsbotschaft auf denjenigen hinterlassen , den ich gewählt habe kty bye	[0, 1, 0]	NOT	{}	{'kty bye': [84, 91, 'PER']}
5354	that can classify termites into specific groupings	die Termiten in spezifische Gruppen klassifizieren können	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
7566	I have a huge penis and I like to fuck icelantic girls in the ass.	Ich habe einen riesigen Penis und ich mag icelantic Mädchen in den Arsch ficken .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
6647	Initial content is what I could glean from Japanese article.	Der ursprüngliche Inhalt ist das , was ich von einem japanischen Artikel sammeln konnte .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Japanese': [43, 51, 'NORP']}	{'japanischen': [53, 64, 'MISC']}
932	He IS in Gay German Nazi Faggots. Please do not delete facts.	Er ist in Gay German Nazi Faggots . Bitte löschen Sie keine Fakten .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'Gay German': [9, 19, 'NORP']}	{'Gay German Nazi Faggots': [10, 33, 'MISC']}
2511	i tried but the chart kept messing up when i changed some of the listed films.	Ich habe versucht , aber die Tabelle hat mich immer wieder verwirrt , als ich einige der aufgelisteten Filme geändert habe .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{}
8136	Where are you trying to get with this? You are not replying to my questions but you continue to block me from having a serious discussion	Wo willst du damit hin ? Du antwortest nicht auf meine Fragen , aber du blockierst mich weiterhin von einer ernsthaften Diskussion .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Wo willst du': [0, 12, 'MISC'], 'du blockierst': [69, 82, 'PER']}
8052	I moved it from the template to the Main page itself for now. See Template talk:Wikipedialang.	Ich habe es von der Vorlage auf die Hauptseite selbst für jetzt verschoben . Siehe Template talk : Wikipedialang .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Main': [36, 40, 'ORG'], 'Wikipedialang': [80, 93, 'PERSON']}	{'Template talk': [83, 96, 'MISC'], 'Wikipedialang': [99, 112, 'LOC']}
8030	Gizmodo link points to Gawker media for some reason..	Gizmodo Link zeigt auf Gawker Medien aus irgendeinem Grund . .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Gizmodo': [0, 7, 'ORG'], 'Gawker': [23, 29, 'ORG']}	{'Gizmodo Link': [0, 12, 'PER'], 'Gawker': [23, 29, 'ORG']}
3032	How are you MudkipsPlz? Or should I call you CHIX0R? Or do you like Angel-of-Losers better?	Wie sind Sie MudkipsPlz ? Oder sollte ich Sie CHIX0R nennen ? Oder gefällt Ihnen Angel - of - Losers besser ?	[1, 1, 0]	ERR	{'MudkipsPlz': [12, 22, 'PERSON']}	{'MudkipsPlz': [13, 23, 'ORG'], 'Angel - of - Losers': [81, 100, 'MISC']}
9331	Shouldn't Ali Carter be at least mid importance on the Wikiproject Snooker scale? He's been in the top 16 for about a decade now surely... {{ }}	Sollte Ali Carter nicht mindestens in der Wikiprojekt - Snooker - Skala von mittlerer Bedeutung sein ? Er ist schon seit ungefähr einem Jahrzehnt in den Top 16 . . . { { } }	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Ali Carter': [10, 20, 'PERSON'], '16': [103, 105, 'CARDINAL'], 'about a decade': [110, 124, 'DATE']}	{'Ali Carter': [7, 17, 'PER']}
2878	He is a convicted murderer. He is no longer an alleged murderer, the trial is over.	Er ist ein verurteilter Mörder . Er ist kein angeblicher Mörder mehr , das Verfahren ist vorbei .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
6526	Lately, there aren't any good IP edits. Time for semi-protection and revisit for 15 to 20 years?	In letzter Zeit gibt es keine guten IP - Bearbeitungen . Zeit für Semi - Schutz und Wiederbesuch für 15 bis 20 Jahre ?	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'IP': [30, 32, 'ORG'], '15 to 20 years': [81, 95, 'DATE']}	{'Zeit für Semi - Schutz und Wiederbesuch': [57, 96, 'MISC']}
7682	Just a few minor comments, so I'm putting the article on hold. Drop me a note if you have any questions.	Nur ein paar kleinere Kommentare , so dass ich den Artikel auf Halt . Drop mir eine Notiz , wenn Sie irgendwelche Fragen haben .	[0, 1, 1]	ERR	{'Drop': [63, 67, 'PERSON']}	{}
443	you were a fool indeed, nanobear, by not helping us. fuck you	du warst wirklich ein Narr , Nanobear , indem du uns nicht halfst . Fick dich	[1, 0, 1]	ERR	{}	{'Nanobear': [29, 37, 'MISC'], 'halfst': [59, 65, 'PER'], 'Fick': [68, 72, 'PER']}
8359	BTW, can you please template me as unblocked, so I can request removal of the autoblock?	BTW , können Sie bitte Vorlage mich als unblocked , so kann ich die Entfernung des Autoblocks anfordern ?	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'BTW': [0, 3, 'ORG']}
9506	I thought Leon Scott Kennedy will appear first time in the film! But finally you said Ada Wong only, WHY?	Ich dachte , Leon Scott Kennedy wird zum ersten Mal im Film erscheinen ! Aber schließlich sagten Sie nur Ada Wong , WHY ?	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Leon Scott Kennedy': [10, 28, 'PERSON'], 'first': [41, 46, 'ORDINAL'], 'Ada Wong': [86, 94, 'PERSON']}	{'Leon Scott Kennedy': [13, 31, 'PER'], 'Ada Wong': [105, 113, 'PER'], 'WHY': [116, 119, 'ORG']}
6155	With nobody having done anything about this for over two years, I've simply made the change.	Da niemand seit mehr als zwei Jahren etwas dagegen getan hat , habe ich einfach den Wandel gemacht .	[1, 0, 1]	ERR	{'two years': [53, 62, 'DATE']}	{}
5667	The bundle will be released in Europe, April 29th.	Das Paket wird am 29 . April in Europa veröffentlicht .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Europe': [31, 37, 'LOC'], 'April 29th': [39, 49, 'DATE']}	{'Europa': [32, 38, 'LOC']}
7139	What the fuck is wrong with you? You say I am a fucking vandal and I havn't done anything. Your bot is fucked up.	Du sagst , ich bin ein verdammter Vandal und ich habe nichts getan . Dein Bot ist gefickt .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{}
9425	SaltyBoatr responds to a message to Kenosis like he is Kenosis - that is plainly obvious! Check the link!	SaltyBoatr reagiert auf eine Nachricht an Kenosis , wie er Kenosis ist - das ist ganz offensichtlich !	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'SaltyBoatr': [0, 10, 'ORG']}	{'SaltyBoatr': [0, 10, 'MISC'], 'Kenosis': [59, 66, 'LOC']}
7022	The apology made was for not following the order of battle, not for the battle itself.	Die Entschuldigung war für die Nichteinhaltung der Schlachtordnung , nicht für die Schlacht selbst .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Schlacht': [83, 91, 'MISC']}
5075	Hi Fimus, did you find my comments of some use. I am rather new here and I would appreciate your response.	Hallo Fimus , fanden Sie meine Kommentare von etwas Gebrauch . Ich bin ziemlich neu hier und ich würde Ihre Antwort schätzen .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Hallo Fimus': [0, 11, 'PER']}
7260	fear my expression will be censored and that I may	fürchte , dass mein Ausdruck zensiert wird und dass ich	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
8432	Yeah, but playing a game in Toronto has nothing to do with adding a Mexican linebacker to the practice squad.	Ja , aber ein Spiel in Toronto zu spielen hat nichts mit einem mexikanischen Linebacker in die Trainingsmannschaft hinzuzufügen zu tun .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Toronto': [28, 35, 'GPE'], 'Mexican': [68, 75, 'NORP']}	{'Toronto': [23, 30, 'LOC'], 'mexikanischen': [63, 76, 'MISC'], 'Trainingsmannschaft': [95, 114, 'MISC']}
9808	Over half of the people agree because the respondents are tired of harrassment from FLG.''''''	Mehr als die Hälfte der Befragten sind damit einverstanden , weil die Befragten von der Belästigung durch die FLG müde sind . ' ' ' ' ' '	[1, 0, 1]	ERR	{'Over half': [0, 9, 'CARDINAL'], 'FLG': [84, 87, 'ORG']}	{'Befragten': [24, 33, 'ORG'], 'FLG': [110, 113, 'ORG']}
4318	Johnny Wears his belt buckle slightly to the left and he has gotten divorced like 5 times but that doesn't make him not hot does it???!!!	Johnny Wears seine Gürtelschnalle leicht nach links und er ist wie 5 mal abgeschieden , aber das macht ihn nicht heiß macht es ? ? ? ! ! !	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'Johnny Wears': [0, 12, 'PERSON'], '5': [82, 83, 'CARDINAL']}	{'Johnny Wears': [0, 12, 'PER']}
5612	Hello, welcome to WP. You may be interested in the discussion on my talk page related to Metropolitan Registries. See: [URL]	Hallo , Willkommen bei WP . Sie könnten an der Diskussion auf meiner Gesprächsseite zu Metropolitan Registries interessiert sein . Siehe : [ URL ]	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'WP': [18, 20, 'ORG'], 'Metropolitan Registries': [89, 112, 'ORG']}	{'WP': [23, 25, 'ORG'], 'Metropolitan Registries': [87, 110, 'ORG']}
6228	Additionally as practice has begun, Charles Pic's presence in the series should become obvious.	Nach dem Beginn der Serie soll auch die Präsenz von Charles Pic in der Serie deutlich werden .	[0, 1, 1]	ERR	"{""Charles Pic's"": [36, 49, 'PERSON']}"	{'Charles Pic': [52, 63, 'PER']}
74	A protest by itself has so much constructive purpose. Admin POV pushing must stop.Prevention is better than cure.	Ein Protest selbst hat so viel konstruktives Ziel . Admin POV drängen muss aufhören . Vorbeugung ist besser als Heilung .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Admin POV': [52, 61, 'MISC']}
7315	Never mind, but if you have time or are involved in the Macedonian or Slovenian Wikipedias, could you make a mirror article? Thanks. Alex	Egal , aber wenn Sie Zeit haben oder sich an den mazedonischen oder slowenischen Wikipedias beteiligen , könnten Sie einen Spiegelartikel machen ? Danke . Alex	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Macedonian': [56, 66, 'NORP'], 'Slovenian': [70, 79, 'NORP'], 'Alex': [133, 137, 'PERSON']}	{'mazedonischen': [49, 62, 'LOC'], 'slowenischen': [68, 80, 'MISC'], 'Wikipedias': [81, 91, 'MISC']}
1386	ocean. In the end, Michael tragically hangs himself while masturbating over his brother's dead body.	Am Ende hängt sich Michael tragisch selbst an , während er über den Leichnam seines Bruders masturbiert .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'Michael': [19, 26, 'PERSON']}	{'Michael': [19, 26, 'PER']}
5913	except for maybe the one with the guns, but that's also a grey area IMO	außer vielleicht der mit den Waffen , aber das ist auch ein graues Gebiet IMO	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'IMO': [74, 77, 'ORG']}
691	that's your opinion. you can keep it to yourself. everyone on the show deserves a page. -	Das ist deine Meinung . Du kannst es dir selbst behalten . Jeder auf der Show verdient eine Seite . -	[1, 1, 0]	ERR	{}	{}
5214	Gee, I could have sworn I posted a constructive comment here. Must have gone into a wormhole, or been fascistisized.	Gee , ich hätte geschworen , ich habe hier einen konstruktiven Kommentar gepostet . Muss in ein Wurmloch gegangen sein , oder wurde fascisiert .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Gee': [0, 3, 'PER']}
1410	YOU DON'T KNOW ABOUT THE HISTORY!!,I THINK YOU ARE THE BIG LOSER	Sie wissen nicht , über die Geschichte ! ! , Ich denke , Sie sind der große Liebhaber	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{}
2820	I am a billionaire, I can use my resources to track you down	Ich bin ein Milliardär , ich kann meine Ressourcen verwenden , um Sie aufzuspüren	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
4375	Hey static, piss off because i provided proof with a link now stop changing every single edit i make you little fairy.	Hey statisch , piss off , weil ich Beweis mit einem Link jetzt stoppen , jede einzelne Änderung ich machen Sie kleine Fee .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'Hey': [0, 3, 'PER'], 'piss off': [15, 23, 'MISC'], 'Link': [52, 56, 'MISC']}
1533	At the height of the Watergate scandal, a polled showed that,	Auf dem Höhepunkt des Watergate - Skandals zeigte eine Umfrage , dass	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Watergate': [21, 30, 'EVENT']}	{'Watergate': [22, 31, 'MISC']}
1469	Hahaha, that is very true. Except the elitists on this site are asskissing morons.	Hahaha , das ist sehr wahr . Außer die Eliten auf dieser Seite sind alsskissing Morons .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'Hahaha': [0, 6, 'MISC'], 'alsskissing Morons': [68, 86, 'PER']}
7548	You're a nuisance. Go conjugate with a pair of maple trees you cocksucking faggot. LULZ LULZ!	Du bist ein Ärgernis . Gehe konjugieren mit einem Paar Ahornbäume du Cocksucking faggot . LULZ LULZ !	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'Gehe': [23, 27, 'MISC'], 'LULZ LULZ': [90, 99, 'ORG']}
4833	No need to worry about that; I got a warning that I'm on my last strike or something before I get blocked. Not like I contribute anyway.	Keine Notwendigkeit , sich darüber zu sorgen ; Ich habe eine Warnung erhalten , dass ich auf meinem letzten Streik oder so etwas bin , bevor ich gesperrt werde . Nicht wie ich trotzdem beitragen .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{}
6996	Description on image page is confusing about this.	Beschreibung auf der Bildseite ist verwirrend darüber .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
9867	Hmm, was unaware of the unsigned thingy. Anyways, I agree with you that the terminology is indeed confusing. Keep up the anti-vandalism work!	Hmm , war mir nicht bewusst , was das unsignierte Ding ist . Jedenfalls bin ich mit Ihnen einverstanden , dass die Terminologie wirklich verwirrend ist . Halten Sie die Anti - vandalism - Arbeit !	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Hmm': [0, 3, 'PER']}
6391	Oh wait should we just change the artwork to the one with just the tiger, i'm confused because different websites are still using both.	Oh warten sollten wir einfach das Kunstwerk auf das mit nur dem Tiger zu ändern , bin ich verwirrt , weil verschiedene Websites immer noch beide verwenden .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Tiger': [64, 69, 'MISC']}
9422	ignoring the consensus of the AfD discussion, and is	ignoriert den Konsens der AfD - Diskussion und ist	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'AfD': [30, 33, 'ORG']}	{'AfD': [26, 29, 'ORG']}
6137	The X Factor live shows Hi, according to Fox's schedule there are no live shows on the 16 or 17th October so stop adding it in.	Die X Factor Live - Shows Hi , laut Fox ' s Zeitplan gibt es keine Live - Shows am 16 . oder 17 . Oktober , also stoppen Sie es hinzuzufügen .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Fox': [41, 44, 'ORG'], '16 or 17th October': [87, 105, 'DATE']}	"{'X Factor Live - Shows Hi': [4, 28, 'MISC'], ""Fox ' s Zeitplan"": [36, 52, 'MISC']}"
7232	I must say that Mira Gambolputty has some, um, innovative interpretations of WP practice and policy.	Ich muss sagen , dass Mira Gambolputty einige , um , innovative Interpretationen von WP - Practice und - Politik hat .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'Mira Gambolputty': [16, 32, 'PERSON'], 'WP': [77, 79, 'ORG']}	{'Mira Gambolputty': [22, 38, 'PER'], 'WP': [85, 87, 'ORG']}
6846	Not actually. Look at Olethros and look up the scriptures that Olethros is in store for goats.	Nicht wirklich . Schauen Sie sich Olethros an und schauen Sie sich die Schriften an , dass Olethros für Ziegen bereit ist .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Olethros': [63, 71, 'ORG']}	{'Olethros': [91, 99, 'PER']}
7092	You overtly undertake bold indignantly grotesque coldness over candid kindheartedness.	Ihr unternehmt offen mutige , verärgernd groteskische Kälte über offene Güte .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
7385	Also, that it is not mainstream among Russian and Chinese physical anthropologists, indicating a lack of consensus.	Auch , dass es nicht der Mainstream unter russischen und chinesischen physikalischen Anthropologen ist , was auf einen Mangel an Konsens hinweist .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Russian': [38, 45, 'NORP'], 'Chinese': [50, 57, 'NORP']}	{'russischen': [42, 52, 'MISC'], 'chinesischen': [57, 69, 'MISC']}
7760	This guy should probably just jump from something.	Dieser Kerl sollte wahrscheinlich einfach von etwas springen .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
5839	This is a work in progress, please do not delete, I plan to update and wikify alot of this by the end of october.	Dies ist eine Arbeit im Gange , bitte nicht löschen , ich plane , zu aktualisieren und wikify viel davon bis Ende Oktober .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'the end of october': [94, 112, 'DATE']}	{'wikify': [87, 93, 'LOC']}
3819	It's got nothing to do with race, it's got everything to do with the fact that Murali is a chucker!	Es hat nichts mit Rasse zu tun , es hat alles mit der Tatsache zu tun , dass Murali ein Schnappschuss ist !	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'Murali': [79, 85, 'PERSON']}	{'Murali': [77, 83, 'PER']}
8144	I POSTED THIS BIO IN THE FIRST PLACE IN DECEMBER!	Ich habe diese BIO am ersten Platz im Dezember veröffentlicht !	[1, 0, 1]	ERR	{'FIRST': [25, 30, 'ORDINAL'], 'DECEMBER': [40, 48, 'DATE']}	{'BIO': [15, 18, 'ORG']}
5786	yes because students are making projects about switzerland and they cant find anything	ja , weil Studenten Projekte über die Schweiz machen und sie nichts finden	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'switzerland': [47, 58, 'GPE']}	{'Schweiz': [38, 45, 'LOC']}
1273	Do you own Wikipedia? I don't fucking think so, Uncle Dick. Girls just wanna have fun! Bywaaaaaaa!	Haben Sie Wikipedia ? Ich glaube nicht , dass so , Onkel Dick . Mädchen wollen einfach Spaß haben ! Bywaaaaaaa !	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'Wikipedia': [11, 20, 'PERSON'], 'Uncle Dick': [48, 58, 'PERSON']}	{'Wikipedia': [10, 19, 'MISC'], 'Dick': [57, 61, 'PER'], 'Bywaaaaaaa': [100, 110, 'PER']}
3940	I've just asked mathematica, and the twelve 9s version is correct.	Ich habe gerade mathematica gefragt , und die zwölf 9s Version ist richtig .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'mathematica': [16, 27, 'ORG'], 'twelve': [37, 43, 'CARDINAL']}	{'mathematica': [16, 27, 'MISC']}
6698	Image removed as copyright has not been established.	Bild entfernt als Urheberrecht wurde nicht festgestellt .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
7286	We give the facts as much weight as reliable sources do - no more and no less. That is what WP:NPOV means.	Wir geben den Fakten so viel Gewicht wie verlässliche Quellen - nicht mehr und nicht weniger . Das ist , was WP : NPOV bedeutet .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'WP': [92, 94, 'ORG']}	{'WP': [109, 111, 'MISC'], 'NPOV': [114, 118, 'ORG']}
7849	Back up your claims with reputable sources. Are you Michael Lafosse in reality?	Sichern Sie Ihre Ansprüche mit seriösen Quellen . Sind Sie Michael Lafosse in Wirklichkeit ?	[0, 1, 1]	ERR	{'Michael Lafosse': [52, 67, 'PERSON']}	{'Michael Lafosse': [59, 74, 'PER']}
7383	I mean: some Callimachi were Romanian, some were not, but they all were dispora.	Ich meine : Einige Callimachi waren Rumänen , einige waren nicht , aber sie waren alle dispora .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Callimachi': [13, 23, 'GPE'], 'Romanian': [29, 37, 'NORP'], 'dispora': [72, 79, 'PERSON']}	{'Callimachi': [19, 29, 'PER'], 'Rumänen': [36, 43, 'LOC'], 'dispora': [87, 94, 'PER']}
1262	I dont have money to do a research of you, stay away	Ich habe kein Geld , um dich zu erforschen , bleibe weg	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
7954	I am working on these things, and as a first step, removing excessive details. Thank you everybody.	Ich arbeite an diesen Dingen , und als erster Schritt beseitige ich übermäßige Details . Vielen Dank .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'first': [39, 44, 'ORDINAL']}	{'Vielen Dank': [89, 100, 'PER']}
6327	REDIRECT Talk:Animal conspiracy theories involving Israel	REDIRECT Talk : Tier Verschwörungstheorien mit Israel	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Israel': [51, 57, 'GPE']}	{'REDIRECT Talk': [0, 13, 'MISC'], 'Israel': [47, 53, 'LOC']}
7076	Actually, it seems the only uses of overline are WP mirrors... -\ Including complex number, which uses overline to mean complex conjugate.	Eigentlich scheint es , dass die einzigen Verwendungen von Overline sind WP Spiegel . . . - \ Inklusive komplexe Zahl , die überline verwendet , um komplexe Konjugieren zu bedeuten .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'WP': [49, 51, 'ORG']}	{'Overline': [59, 67, 'PER'], 'WP Spiegel': [73, 83, 'ORG']}
3884	Written as a campaign article The article needs re-writing as of April 2014 as it is written as a campaign article.	Als Kampagnenartikel geschrieben Der Artikel muss ab April 2014 neu geschrieben werden , da er als Kampagnenartikel geschrieben wird .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'April 2014': [65, 75, 'DATE']}	{}
7417	Thank you for recognizing this and retracting your accusations, not many people on this site admit their mistakes.	Vielen Dank für die Anerkennung dieses und die Rücknahme Ihrer Anschuldigungen , nicht viele Menschen auf dieser Seite zugegeben , ihre Fehler .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Vielen Dank für die Anerkennung': [0, 31, 'MISC']}
4742	And I apologize if I sounded like a curmugeon, but absolute claims do make for some difficulty.	Und ich entschuldige mich , wenn ich wie ein Curmugeon klang , aber absolute Behauptungen machen für einige Schwierigkeiten .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
4243	Enhanced the image to remove glare and bring out detail.	Verbesserte das Bild , um Glanz zu entfernen und Details hervorzubringen .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
2545	Correct, Offender is attempting to rewrite history.	Richtig , Der Täter versucht , die Geschichte neu zu schreiben .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
7	goofs for gods sake people, its a god damned cartoon, not everything has to be correct	goofs für Gott , Leute , es ist eine verdammte Karikatur , nicht alles muss richtig sein	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'goofs': [0, 5, 'PER']}
6763	lol Rita Guerra is a prominent person? this must be some kind of joke	lol Rita Guerra ist eine prominente Person ? das muss eine Art Witz sein	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Rita Guerra': [4, 15, 'PERSON']}	{'lol Rita Guerra': [0, 15, 'PER']}
6679	Actually, all of that section is indexed to one section. Isn't that a red flag of some sort?	Eigentlich ist all dieser Abschnitt auf einen Abschnitt indexiert . Ist das nicht eine rote Flagge irgendeiner Art ?	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'one': [44, 47, 'CARDINAL']}	{}
6639	Wait, if it just took a minute to upload it, why is it still red? (I'm not experienced in image uploading).	Warten Sie , wenn es nur eine Minute dauerte , um es hochzuladen , warum ist es immer noch rot ? ( Ich habe keine Erfahrung im Bild hochzuladen ) .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'a minute': [22, 30, 'TIME']}	{'Warten': [0, 6, 'PER']}
9871	Exactly these are Greeks ( Slavs ,Turks, Jewish, Albanians etc ) do you know any Albanian yourself by any chance ?	Genau das sind Griechen ( Slawen , Türken , Juden , Albaner usw . ) Kennen Sie überhaupt einen Albaner ?	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'Greeks': [18, 24, 'NORP'], 'Slavs': [27, 32, 'NORP'], 'Turks': [34, 39, 'NORP'], 'Jewish': [41, 47, 'NORP'], 'Albanians': [49, 58, 'NORP'], 'Albanian': [81, 89, 'NORP']}	{'Griechen': [15, 23, 'MISC'], 'Slawen': [26, 32, 'MISC'], 'Türken': [35, 41, 'LOC'], 'Juden': [44, 49, 'MISC'], 'Albaner': [95, 102, 'LOC']}
5647	EDIT: It has now gone - I dont know why or how. It doesn't even appear in my offline history... anybody shed any light?	EDIT : Es ist jetzt verschwunden - ich weiß nicht warum oder wie . Es erscheint nicht einmal in meiner Offline - Geschichte . . . jemand shed any light ?	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'EDIT': [0, 4, 'MISC']}
5196	i made love to a BL 7.2 inch Howitzer Mk.I once the other name to them is betty	ich machte Liebe zu einem BL 7 . 2 Zoll Howitzer Mk . I einmal der andere Name zu ihnen ist betty	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Howitzer Mk': [29, 40, 'PERSON']}	{'BL 7': [26, 30, 'MISC'], 'Howitzer Mk': [40, 51, 'MISC'], 'I': [54, 55, 'MISC']}
906	Great detective work typer525 i hope you find that dang vandal.	Große Detektivarbeit typer525 Ich hoffe , dass Sie das Dang Vandal finden .	[0, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'Dang Vandal': [55, 66, 'MISC']}
7579	Boo hoo I've been blocked for a week, big deal, next week I'll be back to editing and that's notta threat, that's a promise.	Boo hoo Ich bin eine Woche lang gesperrt worden , ein großer Deal , nächste Woche werde ich wieder zur Bearbeitung kommen und das ist keine Drohung , das ist ein Versprechen .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'a week': [30, 36, 'DATE'], 'next week': [48, 57, 'DATE']}	{'Boo hoo Ich': [0, 11, 'MISC']}
6816	Cleaned up some info on the general page, the new album is already released!	Einige Informationen auf der allgemeinen Seite aufgeräumt , das neue Album ist bereits erschienen !	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
6956	On a note unrelated to the above - thanks for the change on this page in regard to just war. Many thanks.	Auf einer Notiz , die nicht mit dem oben genannten zusammenhängt - vielen Dank für die Änderung auf dieser Seite in Bezug auf den gerechten Krieg . Vielen Dank .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Krieg': [140, 145, 'MISC'], 'Vielen Dank': [148, 159, 'PER']}
2277	its not my interpretation. that episode is themed after the manga which is shown there as well.	Es ist nicht meine Interpretation . diese Episode ist nach der Manga , die auch dort gezeigt wird , thematisch .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
2486	your lazy ass keeping the admin back log low, RETARD. Your not making a difference, you can't fill a sand bag with all your wonderful edits.	Dein fauler Arsch hält den Admin zurück niedrig , RETARD . Dein nicht ein Unterschied machen , kannst du nicht mit all deinen wunderbaren Bearbeitungen einen Sandbeutel füllen .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'Dein fauler Arsch': [0, 17, 'MISC'], 'RETARD': [50, 56, 'ORG']}
5547	delete the cemetery page. i made it as a vanity page.	Löschen Sie die Friedhofsseite . Ich habe es als eine Eitelkeitsseite gemacht .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Friedhofsseite': [16, 30, 'MISC']}
8701	Some of them were quite minor events. But the removal should not be marked as a minor edit.	Einige von ihnen waren ganz geringfügige Ereignisse . Aber die Entfernung sollte nicht als geringfügige Bearbeitung markiert werden .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
8825	Ah well. Thanks anyway. And I'll check with them.	Ah gut . Vielen Dank trotzdem . Und ich werde mit ihnen überprüfen .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Ah': [0, 2, 'PER']}
4339	Bottom line: it doesn't need a section longer than the rest of the article put together....	Fazit : Es braucht keinen Abschnitt länger als der Rest des Artikels zusammengefasst . . . .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
5	Yes, Sarujo thinks he knows everything yet he knows nothing.	Ja , Sarujo denkt , er weiß alles , aber er weiß nichts .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Sarujo': [5, 11, 'ORG']}	{'Sarujo': [5, 11, 'PER']}
6748	Q - is a moron of the highest order an oxymoron? please tell us gurd ass...	Q - ist ein Narr der höchsten Ordnung ein oxymoron ? bitte sagen Sie uns gurd ass . . .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'Q': [0, 1, 'MISC'], 'gurd ass': [73, 81, 'PER']}
6081	fuck wikipedia, ban me then, i dont care, come wikisuckmedik	ficken wikipedia , verbieten mich dann , ich kümmere mich nicht , kommen wikisuckmedik	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'fuck wikipedia': [0, 14, 'PERSON']}	{'ficken wikipedia': [0, 16, 'PER']}
8592	You need a triple integral up your ass... with cylindrical coordinates. Don't forget to take a divergent of a cum shot in your mouth.	Sie brauchen ein dreifaches Integral auf Ihrem Arsch . . . mit zylindrischen Koordinaten . Vergessen Sie nicht , eine Differenz von einem Cum - Shot in Ihrem Mund zu nehmen .	[1, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Integral': [28, 36, 'MISC']}
5434	Attention Federalist! You are allowed to write nonsense on Talk Pages! WP:NONSENSE	Achtung Federalist ! Sie sind erlaubt , Unsinn auf Talk Pages zu schreiben ! WP : NONSENSE	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'Talk Pages': [59, 69, 'WORK_OF_ART']}	{'Achtung Federalist': [0, 18, 'PER'], 'Talk Pages': [51, 61, 'MISC'], 'WP': [77, 79, 'MISC'], 'NONSENSE': [82, 90, 'MISC']}
3226	listen here buddy, this kyle. I think my cool new page is freakin hilarious, and you should too. don't make me send another message, dad-gum-it!	Ich denke , meine neue coole Seite ist verrückt witzig , und du solltest auch . Mache mich nicht zu einer anderen Nachricht , Papa - gum - it !	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{}
1408	Who and Why keeps deleting the I Stand Alone section	Wer und warum löscht immer wieder den Abschnitt I Stand Alone	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'I': [48, 49, 'MISC'], 'Alone': [56, 61, 'MISC']}
3897	pardon the mentally ill. tom cant help it. he needs help. and he loves black ass.	pardon the mentally ill . Tom kann es nicht helfen . er braucht Hilfe . und er liebt schwarzen Arsch .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'tom': [25, 28, 'PERSON']}	{'pardon the mentally ill': [0, 23, 'PER'], 'Tom': [26, 29, 'MISC']}
7738	You have to add sources to stuff here you dont there	Du musst hier Quellen hinzufügen , du nicht da	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
8248	Umn, that would be intellectual honesty. Not allowed in clique articles. Sorry. But you'll just have to remain blocked.	Umn , das wäre eine intellektuelle Ehrlichkeit . Nicht erlaubt in Clique - Artikeln . Entschuldigung . Aber Sie müssen nur blockiert bleiben .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Umn': [0, 3, 'ORG']}	{'Umn': [0, 3, 'PER']}
4124	Okay then. I'll just have to agree to disagree. I won't read your article and I won't give you fellatio. Now get off my page.	Okay dann . Ich muss nur zustimmen , nicht einverstanden zu sein . Ich werde deinen Artikel nicht lesen und ich werde dir keine Fälschung geben .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Okay': [0, 4, 'PER']}
1869	Winged unicorn You added lots of good information there! I just wish people stopped removing it, the history's full of red!	Winged unicorn Sie haben viele gute Informationen hinzugefügt ! Ich wünsche mir nur , dass die Leute aufhören , es zu entfernen , die Geschichte ist voller rot !	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Winged unicorn': [0, 14, 'MISC']}
7935	No, Symmetric difference, which is its most commn maths usage	Nein , Symmetrische Differenz , die ihr am häufigsten verwendet wird	[0, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{}
1421	How that applies to stuff for 0x10^c as a game is certainly something is not a settled question yet.	Wie sich das auf Sachen für 0x10^c als Spiel bezieht , ist sicherlich noch nicht geklärt .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
7770	I put in another warning on user's talk page. After 4 escalating warnings you can request the user to be banned.	Ich habe eine andere Warnung auf der Benutzer - Talk - Seite . Nach 4 eskalierenden Warnungen können Sie den Benutzer bitten , verboten zu werden .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'4': [52, 53, 'CARDINAL']}	{}
7894	So, what does anyone think about including such a paragraph/section?	Also , was denkt jemand über die Einbeziehung eines solchen Absatzes / Abschnitts ?	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
5734	And a biographical page is intended to contain biographical information, that is, information about one's life.	Und eine biografische Seite soll biographische Informationen enthalten , d . h . Informationen über das eigene Leben .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
2370	since i was blocked, then blackburne reversed it, well than others are majority, even if they are wrong pedos!	da ich blockiert wurde , dann Blackburne es umgekehrt , gut als andere sind Mehrheit , auch wenn sie falsche Pedos !	[0, 1, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Blackburne': [30, 40, 'PER']}
3135	Hi, Could you provide references for your edits to Ethiopian sign languages? Thanks, —	Hallo , Können Sie Referenzen für Ihre Bearbeitungen zu äthiopischen Zeichensprachen bieten ? Vielen Dank , -	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Ethiopian': [51, 60, 'NORP']}	{'äthiopischen': [56, 68, 'MISC']}
8090	But me like it, it is my fav-our-rite. Just like TehKewl likes to smear shit on his chest whilst masturbating to nude pictures of Justin Timberlake.	Aber mir gefällt es , es ist mein Fav - our - rite . Genau wie TehKewl gerne Scheiß auf seiner Brust schmiert , während er nackte Bilder von Justin Timberlake masturbiert .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'TehKewl': [49, 56, 'LAW'], 'Justin Timberlake': [130, 147, 'PERSON']}	{'TehKewl': [63, 70, 'MISC'], 'Justin Timberlake': [141, 158, 'PER']}
4423	I think his criticism applies more to Chandrakirti.	Ich denke , seine Kritik gilt mehr für Chandrakirti .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Chandrakirti': [38, 50, 'PERSON']}	{'Chandrakirti': [39, 51, 'PER']}
4049	I know there are still a lot of red links, but maybe these could be created as stubs.	Ich weiß , dass es immer noch viele rote Links gibt , aber vielleicht könnten diese als Spitzen erstellt werden .	[1, 1, 0]	ERR	{}	{}
4509	Southall in West London is dominated by a variety of Indian cuisines (in the strict sense) because the locals are Hindus from areas of India.	Southall in West London wird von einer Vielzahl von indischen Küchen ( im strengen Sinn ) dominiert , weil die Einheimischen Hindus aus Gebieten Indiens sind .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Southall': [0, 8, 'GPE'], 'West London': [12, 23, 'GPE'], 'Indian': [53, 59, 'NORP'], 'Hindus': [114, 120, 'NORP'], 'India': [135, 140, 'GPE']}	{'Southall': [0, 8, 'PER'], 'West London': [12, 23, 'LOC'], 'indischen': [52, 61, 'MISC'], 'Indiens': [145, 152, 'LOC']}
6361	Sorry, I didn't know. I added a tag, are you able to delete it?	Sorry , ich wusste es nicht . Ich habe ein Tag hinzugefügt , können Sie es löschen ?	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Sorry': [0, 5, 'PER']}
6132	Oh go cuck yourself. Protecting fake users. Coward. Fuck you	Oh go cuck selbst . Schutz von gefälschten Benutzern . Feigling . Ficken Sie	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'Oh go cuck': [0, 10, 'MISC']}
4534	hello everyone I hope someone looks me up anytime soon!	Hallo alle Ich hoffe , dass mich bald jemand anschaut !	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{}
8949	Ritchie Blackmore used the under over technique while playing Smoke on the Water in the 70s, so it shouldn't be listed as an invention of Batio.	Ritchie Blackmore verwendete in den 70er Jahren die Underover - Technik beim Spielen von Smoke on the Water , so dass es nicht als Erfindung von Batio aufgeführt werden sollte .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Ritchie Blackmore': [0, 17, 'PERSON'], 'Smoke': [62, 67, 'ORG']}	{'Ritchie Blackmore': [0, 17, 'PER'], 'Underover': [52, 61, 'MISC'], 'Smoke on the Water': [89, 107, 'ORG'], 'Batio': [145, 150, 'PER']}
9773	In case you forgotten I was already blocked pernamently dumbass.	Falls Sie vergessen , war ich schon blockiert pernamently Dumbass .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'pernamently Dumbass': [46, 65, 'PER']}
2809	Category:Greek mythology * Category:Fundamental physics concepts	Kategorie : Griechische Mythologie * Kategorie : Fundamentale Physik Konzepte	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Greek': [9, 14, 'NORP']}	{'Griechische Mythologie': [12, 34, 'PER']}
9943	FYI I enjoy licking strangers scrotal sacks...especially hairy ones. Yum.	FYI Ich genieße lecken Fremde scrotal Säcke . . . vor allem haarige . Yum .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'FYI Ich genieße lecken Fremde scrotal Säcke': [0, 43, 'MISC'], 'Yum': [70, 73, 'PER']}
5221	The article now answers Mookraker12's question. I got the info by looking at the really large version of the picture.	Der Artikel beantwortet nun die Frage von Mookraker12 . Ich habe die Informationen erhalten , indem ich die wirklich große Version des Bildes sah .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Mookraker12': [24, 35, 'PERSON']}	{}
6161	I'm not sure about the validity of the second purpose of lighting farts, but don't have a problem with it lol.. anyone else?	Ich bin mir nicht sicher über die Gültigkeit des zweiten Zwecks der Beleuchtung von Pards , aber haben Sie kein Problem mit ihm lol . . jemand anderes ?	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'second': [39, 45, 'ORDINAL']}	{'Pards': [84, 89, 'LOC']}
2229	Hey Burgas00, why did you make that personal attack on me on my user page? I found it rather funny:)))	Hey Burgas00 , warum hast du den persönlichen Angriff auf mich auf meiner Benutzerseite gemacht ? Ich fand es ziemlich lustig : ) ) )	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Hey Burgas00': [0, 12, 'PER']}
3193	please is there any email in which we can contact the university of Berlin and how can we apply to the university for law and pharmacy	Bitte gibt es eine E - Mail , in der wir die Universität Berlin kontaktieren können und wie können wir uns an die Universität für Recht und Apotheke bewerben	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'the university of Berlin': [50, 74, 'ORG']}	{'E': [19, 20, 'LOC'], 'Universität Berlin': [45, 63, 'ORG'], 'Universität für Recht und Apotheke': [114, 148, 'ORG']}
3274	tell other editors about yourself, you can do it on . If you want to	erzählen Sie anderen Redakteuren über sich selbst , können Sie es auf . Wenn Sie wollen ,	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
6743	Hey moron, I could easily log out and make edits with another username, and oh 72 hours I'm scared. Moron.	Hey Narr , ich könnte mich einfach ausloggen und mit einem anderen Benutzernamen bearbeiten , und oh 72 Stunden bin ich erschrocken . Narr .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'72 hours': [79, 87, 'TIME']}	{'Hey Narr': [0, 8, 'PER'], 'Narr': [134, 138, 'PER']}
5321	link to The Historical Author of Anong Bahumono In Abi Local Government Area Cross River State, Nigeria	Link zu The Historical Author von Anong Bahumono In Abi Local Government Area Cross River State , Nigeria	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'The Historical Author': [8, 29, 'WORK_OF_ART'], 'Anong Bahumono': [33, 47, 'PERSON'], 'Abi Local Government Area Cross River State': [51, 94, 'ORG'], 'Nigeria': [96, 103, 'GPE']}	{'Link': [0, 4, 'PER'], 'The Historical Author': [8, 29, 'MISC'], 'Anong Bahumono': [34, 48, 'PER'], 'Abi Local Government Area Cross River State': [52, 95, 'LOC'], 'Nigeria': [98, 105, 'LOC']}
8914	Here is a reference to the official fact of the amount of compensation having been agreed between Lucia and the Public Ministry. .	Hier ist ein Hinweis auf die offizielle Tatsache , dass die Höhe der Entschädigung zwischen Lucia und dem Öffentlichen Ministerium vereinbart wurde . .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Lucia': [98, 103, 'PERSON'], 'the Public Ministry': [108, 127, 'ORG']}	{'Lucia': [92, 97, 'PER'], 'Öffentlichen Ministerium': [106, 130, 'ORG']}
8953	Will you stop calling me KL or I'll annoy you like a bat hearing sonic sounds. Read my page first	Willst du aufhören , mich KL zu nennen , oder werde ich dich verärgern wie eine Fledermaus , die sonische Töne hört .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'first': [92, 97, 'ORDINAL']}	{'Willst du aufhören': [0, 18, 'MISC']}
8625	Who are YOU to tell ME??!! I'll do WHAT I like WHEN I like...cocksucker!!	Wer bist Du , um mir zu sagen ? ? ! ! Ich werde tun , was ich mag , wenn ich mag . . . cocksucker ! !	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'cocksucker !': [87, 99, 'ORG']}
7193	FYI hahahahaha - you posted a link to an article on cave diving. Can't you do ANYTHING right, you buffoon?	FYI hahahahaha - Sie haben einen Link zu einem Artikel über Höhlentauchen gepostet . Können Sie nichts richtig machen , du Büffel ?	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'FYI': [0, 3, 'MISC'], 'Link': [33, 37, 'MISC']}
3574	religious debates between christian and muslim scholars,	religiöse Debatten zwischen christlichen und muslimischen Gelehrten ,	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'christian': [26, 35, 'NORP'], 'muslim': [40, 46, 'NORP']}	{'christlichen': [28, 40, 'MISC']}
7572	he stalking the page White Latin Americans, the patterns are the same, he observed who edited	er verfolgte die Seite Weiße Lateinamerikaner , die Muster sind die gleichen , beobachtete er , wer bearbeitete	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'White Latin': [21, 32, 'NORP'], 'Americans': [33, 42, 'NORP']}	{}
4469	I was being sarcastic TV.com is a reliable source. I am just asking for these two things. Please.	Ich war sarkastisch TV . com ist eine zuverlässige Quelle . Ich bitte nur um diese beiden Dinge . Bitte .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'two': [78, 81, 'CARDINAL']}	{}
9785	The british media does not use the term british isles nor does the media in any country i have been to so your facs seem to be outdated.	Die britischen Medien verwenden nicht den Begriff britische Inseln noch die Medien in jedem Land , in dem ich gewesen bin , so dass Ihre Gesichter scheinen veraltet zu sein .	[1, 0, 0]	NOT	{'british': [40, 47, 'NORP']}	{'britischen': [4, 14, 'MISC'], 'britische Inseln': [50, 66, 'LOC']}
1697	Also, I have been accused of having a vandalism only account, however, I have Contributed to several articles anonymously and my account.}}	Auch wurde ich beschuldigt , nur ein Vandalismus Konto zu haben , jedoch habe ich anonym zu mehreren Artikeln und meinem Konto beigetragen . } }	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
4185	I am not from vietnam, nor do i appreciate being called a bitter bee. Please stop the personal attacks.	Ich bin nicht aus Vietnam , noch schätze ich es , als bittere Biene genannt zu werden . Bitte stoppen Sie die persönlichen Angriffe .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'vietnam': [14, 21, 'GPE']}	{'Vietnam': [18, 25, 'LOC']}
8357	The same goes for the rest of your Gundam pictures. I also note that I'm not the first complainer.	Das gleiche gilt für den Rest Ihrer Gundam - Bilder . Ich stelle auch fest , dass ich nicht der erste Beschwerdeführer bin .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Gundam': [35, 41, 'PERSON'], 'first': [81, 86, 'ORDINAL']}	{}
2190	hey!!!!!!! thank you for re-editing my contributions it was really kind of you!!!!!!! i hope you get bowel cancer	hey ! ! ! ! ! ! ! danke für die Neubearbeitung meiner Beiträge es war wirklich freundlich von Ihnen ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ich hoffe , dass Sie Darmkrebs bekommen	[1, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'hey ! ! ! ! ! !': [0, 15, 'ORG']}
4349	My guess is the webmaster just used a generic commercial template.	Meine Vermutung ist , dass der Webmaster nur eine allgemeine kommerzielle Vorlage verwendet .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
1091	I think the questionable links arte important for explaining, where the person has been during the war, which the items concerned.	Ich denke , dass die fraglichen Links arte wichtig für die Erklärung , wo die Person während des Krieges gewesen ist , die betreffenden Gegenstände .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Krieges': [97, 104, 'MISC']}
3089	Uber reverted links which we already agreed upon.	Uber hat Links umgekehrt , die wir bereits vereinbart haben .	[0, 1, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Uber': [0, 4, 'PER']}
742	Listen asshole, you do NOT delete my pages. I do not delete yours so don't delete mine. Understand?	Höre Scheiße , du lösche nicht meine Seiten . Ich lösche nicht deine , also lösche nicht meine . Verstehen Sie ?	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'Höre Scheiße': [0, 12, 'MISC']}
1785	Another thing you may like to try: do you get popups on this page in Safari? I'm using that library to generate the popups.	Eine andere Sache , die Sie vielleicht versuchen möchten : Erhalten Sie Popups auf dieser Seite in Safari ? Ich verwende diese Bibliothek , um die Popups zu generieren .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Safari': [69, 75, 'ORG']}	{'Safari': [99, 105, 'MISC']}
605	please read what i have left there for comments, thanks Ps:it ́s not vandalizing introducing someone ́s ethnicity	Bitte lesen Sie , was ich dort für Kommentare hinterlassen habe , danke Ps : es ist nicht vandalisierend , jemanden die ethnische Zugehörigkeit einzuführen	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Ps': [72, 74, 'MISC']}
2281	More Information I need more information on haus of gaga, so please anyone with information, pics or references, please add them. YZJay	Mehr Informationen Ich brauche mehr Informationen über haus von gaga , so bitte jeder mit Informationen , Bildern oder Referenzen , bitte fügen Sie sie hinzu . YZJay	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'YZJay': [130, 135, 'PERSON']}	{'haus von gaga': [55, 68, 'LOC'], 'YZJay': [160, 165, 'MISC']}
9358	walkers constitutes a NPOV violation if there ever was one.	Wanderer stellt eine NPOV Verletzung dar , wenn es jemals eine gab .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'NPOV': [22, 26, 'GPE']}	{'Wanderer': [0, 8, 'ORG'], 'NPOV': [21, 25, 'ORG']}
1482	IPA aside, what the heck kind of hick pronunciation is that? Sinjun's Wert, really?	Abgesehen von der IPA , was für eine verdammte Aussprache ist das ? Sinjun ' s Wert , wirklich ?	[0, 0, 1]	NOT	{'IPA': [0, 3, 'ORG'], 'Sinjun': [61, 67, 'PERSON'], 'Wert': [70, 74, 'PERSON']}	{'IPA': [18, 21, 'ORG'], 'Sinjun': [68, 74, 'PER']}
4667	Scum editor Bob Rayner is at it again, and I have reverted his edits again (since he obviously did not read the source I cited).	Scum - Editor Bob Rayner ist wieder dabei , und ich habe seine Bearbeitungen wieder zurückgekehrt ( da er offensichtlich nicht die Quelle gelesen habe , die ich zitiert habe ) .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'Bob Rayner': [12, 22, 'PERSON']}	{'Scum - Editor Bob Rayner': [0, 24, 'MISC']}
6583	That way the reader can read both and see that the event was not completely real, but at the same time, not completely false.	Auf diese Weise kann der Leser beide lesen und sehen , dass das Ereignis nicht ganz real war , aber gleichzeitig nicht ganz falsch .	[1, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
1529	Why dont you check Wikireaders comments and then teach me what civility means ?	Warum nicht überprüfen Sie Wikireaders Kommentare und dann lehren Sie mich , was Zivilität bedeutet ?	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Wikireaders Kommentare': [27, 49, 'MISC'], 'Zivilität': [81, 90, 'LOC']}
6713	Assume good faith on your part? You cleary didn't do that for me, you removed the valid categories for no reason whatsoever.	Nehmen Sie guten Glauben auf Ihrer Seite ? Sie cleary nicht , dass für mich , Sie entfernten die gültigen Kategorien ohne Grund überhaupt .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{}
2331	I Will Not Take The Info Away However(It Was 50% Good And 50% Bad) Untill Someone Agrees With Me.	Ich werde die Info jedoch nicht wegnehmen ( es war 50% gut und 50% schlecht ) bis jemand mit mir einverstanden ist .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'50%': [58, 61, 'PERCENT'], 'Untill Someone': [67, 81, 'PERSON']}	{'Info': [14, 18, 'MISC']}
7148	According to another Reba website, the song was written ONLY for the show and for that episode in particular. Hope this helps.	Laut einer anderen Reba - Website wurde der Song nur für die Show und insbesondere für diese Episode geschrieben . Hoffentlich hilft das .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Reba': [21, 25, 'ORG']}	{'Reba': [19, 23, 'ORG']}
1322	k thank you but try to put some his new pics of mohombi tcz	k Vielen Dank aber versuchen , einige seine neuen Bilder von mohombi tcz	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'k Vielen Dank': [0, 13, 'PER'], 'mohombi tcz': [61, 72, 'PER']}
4574	Hi Hiroyuki Yabe, Am surprised there is a Yabe in Japan because am also Yabe.This name is considered Zambian. FROM MUTALE YABE mutaleby@yahoo.com	Hi Hi Hiroyuki Yabe , Ich bin überrascht , dass es einen Yabe in Japan gibt , weil ich auch Yabe bin . Dieser Name wird als Zambian angesehen .	[0, 0, 1]	NOT	{'Hiroyuki Yabe': [3, 16, 'PERSON'], 'Yabe': [72, 76, 'PERSON'], 'Japan': [50, 55, 'GPE'], 'Zambian': [101, 108, 'NORP'], 'MUTALE': [115, 121, 'ORG'], 'YABE': [122, 126, 'PERSON'], 'mutaleby@yahoo.com': [127, 145, 'PRODUCT']}	{'Hi Hi Hiroyuki Yabe': [0, 19, 'PER'], 'Japan': [65, 70, 'LOC'], 'Yabe': [92, 96, 'PER'], 'Zambian': [124, 131, 'PER']}
3591	Hopefully if we can get T25 its own article this wont be a problem here.	Hoffentlich , wenn wir T25 seinen eigenen Artikel bekommen können , wird dies hier kein Problem sein .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'T25': [23, 26, 'MISC']}
9327	I have a copy of the 'Encyclopedia of Rugby League Players', this will have all of John Quayle's stats. I will try and add them soon.	Ich habe eine Kopie der ' Enzyklopädie der Rugby - League - Spieler ' , dies wird alle Statistiken von John Quayle haben . Ich werde versuchen , sie bald hinzuzufügen .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	"{""John Quayle's"": [83, 96, 'PERSON']}"	{'Enzyklopädie der Rugby - League': [26, 57, 'MISC'], 'John Quayle': [103, 114, 'PER']}
5068	one more source of the battle of chamkaur [URL] i want you to edit this Article	eine weitere Quelle der Schlacht von Chamkaur [ URL ] ich möchte , dass Sie diesen Artikel bearbeiten	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'one': [0, 3, 'CARDINAL']}	{'Schlacht von Chamkaur': [24, 45, 'MISC']}
6473	Moreover, none of the sources identify COCOF Assembly as a body required to vote on the ratification.	Darüber hinaus identifiziert keiner der Quellen die COCOF - Versammlung als ein Gremium , das über die Ratifizierung abstimmen muss .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'COCOF Assembly': [39, 53, 'ORG']}	{'COCOF - Versammlung': [52, 71, 'MISC']}
1579	I have already apologized and now working here like everyone else. Why are you still to agressive toward me?	Ich habe mich schon entschuldigt und arbeite jetzt hier wie alle anderen . Warum sind Sie immer noch zu agressiv zu mir ?	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
1503	Tyra [Juola] Szpara has been named one of the best teachers in the United States. She teachs at Holt Junior High School in Holt Michigan.	Tyra [ Juola ] Szpara ist eine der besten Lehrer in den Vereinigten Staaten . Sie unterrichtet an der Holt Junior High School in Holt Michigan .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Tyra': [0, 4, 'PERSON'], 'one': [35, 38, 'CARDINAL'], 'the United States': [63, 80, 'GPE'], 'Holt Junior High School': [96, 119, 'ORG'], 'Holt Michigan': [123, 136, 'GPE']}	{'Tyra [ Juola ] Szpara': [0, 21, 'PER'], 'Vereinigten Staaten': [56, 75, 'LOC'], 'Holt Junior High School': [102, 125, 'MISC'], 'Holt Michigan': [129, 142, 'LOC']}
4022	This should be a disambig page. There are 3 munros of this name and several lesser hills elsewhere in Scotland of the same name.	Dies sollte eine disambig Seite sein . Es gibt 3 Munros mit diesem Namen und mehrere kleinere Hügel anderswo in Schottland mit dem gleichen Namen .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'3': [42, 43, 'CARDINAL'], 'Scotland': [102, 110, 'GPE']}	{'Schottland': [112, 122, 'LOC']}
9439	Looks like I could use some backup on getting a macron into malāsana on the mālāsana page. [URL]	Es scheint , als könnte ich einige Backups verwenden , um ein Makron in malāsana auf der mālāsana Seite zu bekommen . [ URL ]	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Makron': [62, 68, 'PER'], 'malāsana': [72, 80, 'LOC']}
1586	I'm sorry that you have been rude and insulting at every turn INCLUDING this one.	Ich entschuldige mich , dass Sie unhöflich und beleidigend zu jeder Wende gewesen sind , einschließlich dieser .	[1, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Wende': [68, 73, 'MISC']}
6167	How differs a road-killed lawyer from a road-kill skunk? Skid marks are before the skunk.	Wie unterscheidet sich ein Straßenverwundeter Anwalt von einem Straßenverwundeten Skunk ? Skid - Marken sind vor dem Skunk .	[3, 1, 1]	ERR	{'Skid marks': [57, 67, 'PERSON']}	{'Straßenverwundeter': [27, 45, 'PER']}
9342	It's a player market. Jagex or Blizzard have no direct control over it at all.	Es ist ein Spielermarkt . Jagex oder Blizzard haben keinerlei direkte Kontrolle darüber .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Jagex': [22, 27, 'ORG'], 'Blizzard': [31, 39, 'ORG']}	{'Jagex': [26, 31, 'MISC'], 'Blizzard': [37, 45, 'ORG']}
9640	and being a female you are acting so cruel which is surprising	und als weiblich verhalten Sie sich so grausam , was überraschend ist	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
6719	TY, i wish there was somethng that could be done about EKS and his asshole ways	TY , ich wünschte , es wäre somethng , dass über EKS und seine verrückten Wege getan werden könnte	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'TY': [0, 2, 'ORG']}	{'TY': [0, 2, 'MISC'], 'EKS': [49, 52, 'MISC']}
7676	Wow dude. As your physician I suggest you slit your wrists.	Wow dude . Als dein Arzt empfehle ich dir deine Handgelenke zu schneiden .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'Wow dude': [0, 8, 'ORG']}
8610	P.S. A very special thanks to Phantis Wiki for various player bios.	P . S . Ein ganz besonderes Dankeschön an Phantis Wiki für verschiedene Spieler Biografien .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'P.S.': [0, 4, 'PERSON'], 'Phantis Wiki': [30, 42, 'PERSON']}	{'P': [0, 1, 'LOC'], 'S': [4, 5, 'LOC'], 'Phantis': [42, 49, 'PER']}
6375	Oh, but you're happy to do so when it's in defense of your boyfriend Aquaman.	Oh , aber du bist glücklich , das zu tun , wenn es zur Verteidigung deines Freunds Aquaman ist .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Aquaman': [69, 76, 'PERSON']}	{'Aquaman': [83, 90, 'MISC']}
551	I don't think that's right. Isn't there a locality adjustment that does in there?	Ich denke nicht , dass das richtig ist . Gibt es nicht eine Lokalitätsanpassung , die darin tut ?	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
5180	I'm giving up on this one. Wikipedia not only censors its articles, but it removes comments. Happy truthiness, Wikipedia. What a joke you are.	Ich gebe auf diese . Wikipedia zensiert nicht nur ihre Artikel , sondern entfernt Kommentare . Glückliche Wahrhaftigkeit , Wikipedia . Was für ein Witz du bist .	[1, 0, 1]	ERR	{'Wikipedia': [111, 120, 'PERSON']}	{'Wikipedia': [123, 132, 'MISC']}
7906	I have replied to your request on your talk page.	Ich habe auf Ihre Anfrage auf Ihrer Gesprächsseite antwortet .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
2587	Only two people had supported a move before I restored the original and the debate was in process so this is an unreasoned block.	Nur zwei Personen hatten einen Schritt unterstützt , bevor ich das Original wiederherstellte , und die Debatte war im Gange , so dass dies ein unvernünftiger Block ist .	[1, 1, 0]	ERR	{'Only two': [0, 8, 'CARDINAL']}	{}
1709	FYI, Category:Kurdish inhabited region has been moved to Category:Kurdish inhabited regions	FYI , Kategorie : Kurdisch bewohnte Region wurde in Kategorie : Kurdisch bewohnte Regionen verlegt	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Kurdish': [66, 73, 'NORP']}	{'FYI': [0, 3, 'MISC'], 'Kurdisch': [64, 72, 'MISC']}
7705	Adelong wasnt settled in the 1840s. Stop making stuff up.	Adelong wurde nicht in den 1840er Jahren besiedelt . Stoppen Sie , Dinge zu machen .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Adelong': [0, 7, 'PERSON'], 'the 1840s': [25, 34, 'DATE']}	{'Adelong': [0, 7, 'PER']}
5141	Hello. Just don't tell me I'm wrong and it'll be fine...	Hallo . Sage mir einfach nicht , dass ich mich geirrt habe und es wird in Ordnung sein . . .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
1610	I have accepted your apology. Maybe our paths will cross again. May the force be with you.	Ich habe Ihre Entschuldigung akzeptiert . Vielleicht werden unsere Wege wieder kreuzen . Möge die Kraft bei Ihnen sein .	[1, 1, 0]	ERR	{}	{}
9589	Fine! I see you're not gonna work with me here! Screw you then!	Fine ! Ich sehe , dass du hier nicht mit mir arbeiten wirst ! Scheiße dich dann !	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'Screw': [48, 53, 'PERSON']}	{'Fine ! Ich': [0, 10, 'ORG']}
5159	Alhanuty you arab fucker act like a true muslim if you want me blocked, NIGGER!!!!!!!!!!!!!!	Alhanuty du arabischer ficker handeln wie ein echter muslim , wenn du mich blockieren willst , NIGGER ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! !	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Alhanuty': [0, 8, 'PERSON'], 'muslim': [41, 47, 'NORP']}	{'Alhanuty du arabischer ficker': [0, 29, 'PER'], 'NIGGER ! ! ! ! ! ! ! !': [95, 117, 'ORG']}
8121	We're talking about the Matilda chapel image, an obvious mediaeval painting.	Wir sprechen von dem Bild der Matilda Kapelle , einer offensichtlichen mittelalterlichen Malerei .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Matilda': [24, 31, 'ORG']}	{'Matilda': [30, 37, 'MISC'], 'mittelalterlichen': [71, 88, 'MISC']}
6582	I am refering to List of Chinese languages and dialects.	Ich beziehe mich auf Liste der chinesischen Sprachen und Dialekte .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Chinese': [25, 32, 'NORP']}	{'Ich beziehe mich auf Liste der chinesischen Sprachen': [0, 52, 'MISC']}
811	STOP right now, thank you very much. I need somebady with a human touch. Hey you, always on the run, gunna track somebody gonna have some fun!	STOP jetzt , vielen Dank . Ich brauche einigebady mit einer menschlichen Berührung . Hey Sie , immer auf dem Laufen , gunna Track jemand wird etwas Spaß haben !	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'STOP': [0, 4, 'MISC']}
4524	This article makes PETA look like saints. I put a neutrality tag on the article, but some PETA dude put it down.	Dieser Artikel macht PETA wie Heilige aussehen . Ich habe einen Neutralitäts - Tag auf den Artikel gesetzt , aber einige PETA - Dude legte ihn nieder .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'PETA': [19, 23, 'PERSON']}	{'PETA': [121, 125, 'ORG'], 'Dude': [128, 132, 'PER']}
6821	I'm sorry but I have to go now as I am constipated and must use the bathroom.	Es tut mir leid , aber ich muss jetzt gehen , da ich verstopft bin und das Badezimmer benutzen muss .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
4169	How does it feel to be a stupid bitch who edits wikipedia? too bad nobody will ever love you	Wie fühlt es sich an , eine dumme Hündin zu sein , die wikipedia bearbeitet ? zu schlecht , dass niemand dich jemals lieben wird	[1, 0, 1]	ERR	{'wikipedia': [48, 57, 'PERSON']}	{'wikipedia': [55, 64, 'MISC']}
722	Also, the DVD usually has special features that can have additional background.	Außerdem hat die DVD in der Regel spezielle Funktionen , die zusätzlichen Hintergrund haben können .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
7818	Can you please stop blocking me, NinjaOng a.k.a. Ong Ning Jia	Können Sie bitte aufhören , mich zu blockieren , NinjaOng a . k . a . Ong Ning Jia	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'NinjaOng': [33, 41, 'ORG'], 'Ong Ning Jia': [49, 61, 'PERSON']}	{'NinjaOng': [49, 57, 'MISC'], 'Ong Ning Jia': [70, 82, 'PER']}
764	Oh no, please fweddy pwease don't block me i will have no meaning left in my life, LOL you pleb	Oh nein , bitte fweddy pwease blockiere mich nicht ich habe keine Bedeutung mehr in meinem Leben , LOL du pleb	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'LOL du pleb': [99, 110, 'MISC']}
1983	No such polls exist and there is nothing in Wikipedia policy to suggest they are necessary.	Es gibt keine derartigen Umfragen und es gibt nichts in der Wikipedia - Politik , um zu suggerieren , dass sie notwendig sind .	[1, 0, 1]	ERR	{'Wikipedia': [44, 53, 'ORG']}	{'Wikipedia': [60, 69, 'MISC']}
8218	If they actually are public domain, why was it necessary to get the permission of Ralf Hartemink?	Wenn sie tatsächlich öffentliches Domäne sind , warum war es notwendig , die Genehmigung von Ralf Hartemink zu erhalten ?	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Ralf Hartemink': [82, 96, 'PERSON']}	{'Ralf Hartemink': [93, 107, 'PER']}
9687	Even dogs act as lion in there own area. Sitush you are misusing ur administrator power on this page.	Auch Hunde handeln als Löwe in dort eigenem Bereich . Sitush Sie missbrauchen ur Administrator Macht auf dieser Seite .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Sitush': [41, 47, 'PERSON']}	{'Sitush': [54, 60, 'PER']}
9849	So what? The Carpenters have sold more! 150 million!	So was ? Die Carpenters haben mehr verkauft ! 150 Millionen !	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Carpenters': [13, 23, 'PERSON'], '150 million': [40, 51, 'CARDINAL']}	{'Carpenters': [13, 23, 'ORG']}
7723	I have requested mediation between RK and myself and/or Zero. See Wikipedia:Requests for mediation.	Ich habe Mediation zwischen RK und mir und / oder Zero beantragt . Siehe Wikipedia : Requests for mediation .	[0, 0, 1]	NOT	{'RK': [35, 37, 'ORG'], 'Wikipedia': [66, 75, 'PERSON']}	{'RK': [28, 30, 'MISC'], 'Zero': [50, 54, 'MISC'], 'Wikipedia': [73, 82, 'MISC']}
8579	if there is a chromosone then e=what is it? Small Text	Wenn es eine Chromosone gibt , dann e=was ist es ? Kleiner Text	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
4617	lemme see your asshole your asshole your asshole baby!	lemme sehen dein Arschloch dein Arschloch dein Arschloch Baby !	[1, 0, 1]	ERR	{}	{}
8605	nb: might was well acknowledge that this was me; 'me' being the user now known as . Cheers,	nb : Vielleicht war gut zu erkennen , dass dies war ich ; ' me ' ist der Benutzer jetzt bekannt als . Cheers ,	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'nb': [0, 2, 'ORG'], 'Cheers': [102, 108, 'MISC']}
7569	All of these sources are listed by Sourcewatch. They are not worthy of being used as a source on WIKI.	Alle diese Quellen sind von Sourcewatch aufgelistet . Sie sind nicht wert , als Quelle auf WIKI verwendet zu werden .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Sourcewatch': [35, 46, 'PERSON']}	{'Sourcewatch': [28, 39, 'LOC'], 'WIKI': [91, 95, 'MISC']}
989	Oppose - Hanja and Sino-Korean vocabulary are CLEARLY distinctive categories, just like Romances languages and Latin should be separated.	Gegenüber - Hanja und das chinesisch - koreanische Wortschatz sind eindeutig unterschiedliche Kategorien , genau wie Römische Sprachen und Latein sollten getrennt werden .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'Sino-Korean': [19, 30, 'NORP'], 'Latin': [111, 116, 'NORP']}	{'chinesisch': [26, 36, 'MISC'], 'koreanische': [39, 50, 'MISC'], 'Latein': [139, 145, 'MISC']}
4110	other people's Gosh you can't even speak English which you claim to be your mother tongue. Puh-lease.	andere Leute ' s Gosh du kannst nicht einmal Englisch sprechen , die du behauptest , deine Muttersprache zu sein . Puh - lease .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'English': [41, 48, 'LANGUAGE']}	{'Englisch': [45, 53, 'MISC']}
2665	C. Fred THANKS SO SO MUCH. I WILL ADD MORE REFERENCES ON MONDAY. SHE HAS TONS! THANKS SO SO MUCH!	C . Fred dankt so sehr . Ich werde am Montag noch mehr Referenzen hinzufügen . Sie hat Tonnen ! dankt so sehr !	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'C. Fred': [0, 7, 'PERSON'], 'MONDAY': [57, 63, 'DATE']}	{'C': [0, 1, 'MISC'], 'Fred': [4, 8, 'PER']}
1103	But is the C code actually readable, keeping comments etc.? That one of Pascal or GHC probably is not...	Aber ist der C - Code tatsächlich lesbar , hält Kommentare usw . ? Das ist Pascal oder GHC wahrscheinlich nicht . . .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Pascal': [72, 78, 'PERSON']}	{'C': [13, 14, 'MISC'], 'Pascal': [75, 81, 'MISC'], 'GHC': [87, 90, 'MISC']}
6673	How about examples of some of the more famous rational numbers, like Pi and e?	Wie wäre es mit Beispielen einiger berühmter rationaler Zahlen , wie Pi und e ?	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Pi': [69, 71, 'MISC']}
5895	I'm happy to announce that I'm back online. With my dynamic IP I can easily bypass your blocks wiki-pedos.	Ich bin glücklich zu verkünden , dass ich wieder online bin . Mit meiner dynamischen IP kann ich leicht Ihre Blöcke Wiki - Pedos umgehen .	[1, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
781	Shit!!! Shit!!! Fuck you!!! you're son of a bitch!!!	Scheiße ! ! ! Scheiße ! ! ! Scheiße dich ! ! ! Du bist ein Scheißeohn ! ! !	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'Scheiße ! ! ! Scheiße ! ! ! Scheiße dich ! ! ! Du bist ein Scheißeohn': [0, 69, 'ORG']}
6810	As a citation, would you need something like a PDF document?	Als Zitat , würden Sie etwas wie ein PDF - Dokument benötigen ?	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'PDF': [47, 50, 'ORG']}	{'PDF': [37, 40, 'MISC']}
4546	So, is it totally dead or we have a chance to see it sometime?	Also , ist es total tot oder haben wir eine Chance , es irgendwann zu sehen ?	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
5704	I value your point of view. Thank you for the answer.	Ich schätze Ihren Standpunkt . Vielen Dank für die Antwort .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
8932	Many of the listed bombing raids were made in response to similar German raids, but this really does have very little to do with Trenchard.	Viele der aufgeführten Bombenangriffe wurden in Reaktion auf ähnliche deutsche Angriffe durchgeführt , aber das hat wirklich wenig mit Trenchard zu tun .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'German': [66, 72, 'NORP'], 'Trenchard': [129, 138, 'PERSON']}	{'deutsche': [70, 78, 'MISC']}
7283	And the issue isn't about NRHPs - it's about US county-level stub tags, as you can see from my other additions to the section.	Und das Problem geht nicht um NRHPs - es geht um US - County - Level - stub - Tags , wie Sie von meinen anderen Ergänzungen zu diesem Abschnitt sehen können .	[0, 1, 0]	NOT	{'US': [45, 47, 'GPE']}	{'US': [49, 51, 'LOC']}
9705	Looks like there are two premier pages. See Premier (automobile). Are these the same?	Es sieht aus wie es zwei Premier - Seiten gibt . Siehe Premier ( Automobile ) . Sind diese gleich ?	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'two': [21, 24, 'CARDINAL']}	{'Premier': [55, 62, 'ORG']}
1559	Please add all new information for this section first to the subarticle Government policies and the subprime mortgage crisis.	Bitte fügen Sie alle neuen Informationen für diesen Abschnitt zuerst in den Unterteil Regierungspolitik und Subprime - Hypothekenkrise hinzu .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'first': [48, 53, 'ORDINAL']}	{}
1378	Quit vandalizing the pages or you will be blocked.-	Beenden Sie die Vernichtung der Seiten oder Sie werden blockiert werden . -	[1, 1, 0]	ERR	{'Quit': [0, 4, 'PERSON']}	{}
6383	And finally, I suspect I am beginning to understand the purpose of the respect to our subject.	Und schließlich vermute ich , dass ich den Zweck des Respekts gegen unser Subjekt zu verstehen beginne .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
4436	You have been blocked for 24 hours for vandalism.	Sie wurden für 24 Stunden wegen Vandalismus gesperrt .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'24 hours': [26, 34, 'TIME']}	{}
987	Indeed. Again, thanks for the help. PacificWarrior101	In der Tat . Nochmals vielen Dank für die Hilfe . PacificWarrior101	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
6817	fucking nob knight. Now fuck off and go vandalise something else fuck face	ficken nob knight . jetzt ficken ab und gehen vandalise etwas anderes ficken Gesicht	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'fucking nob knight': [0, 18, 'PERSON']}	{'ficken nob knight': [0, 17, 'MISC']}
2844	I do not know how to sign up is all I am not anonoymus	Ich weiß nicht , wie ich mich anmelden ist alles , was ich bin nicht anonoymus	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
6729	I no longer have his email, but his comments were very interesting.	Ich habe seine E - Mail nicht mehr , aber seine Kommentare waren sehr interessant .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'E': [15, 16, 'LOC']}
6013	Very funny. Censoring 95% of the criticism is not remotely helpful, and you provided no better explanations.	Sehr lustig . 95% der Kritik zu zensieren , ist gar nicht hilfreich , und Sie haben keine besseren Erklärungen gegeben .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'95%': [22, 25, 'PERCENT']}	{}
9298	You both seem to have a pattern of systematically violate policy and then say sorry. This has gotten too old.	Sie beide scheinen ein Muster zu haben , die Politik systematisch zu verletzen und dann zu entschuldigen . Dies ist zu alt geworden .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{}
2047	how dare you i did research dont you know who i am	wie wagst du , ich habe recherchiert weißt du nicht , wer ich bin	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
3422	Return fire? What is this? A shooting match? You want to discuss like civil people or continue regarding this as threats and accusations?	Rückfeuer ? Was ist das ? Ein Schießspiel ? Sie wollen wie Zivilpersonen diskutieren oder darüber als Drohungen und Anschuldigungen weitergehen ?	[0, 1, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Rückfeuer': [0, 9, 'MISC']}
9906	Why can't you just accept the truth and the facts given to you by one of the most authoritive sources?!	Warum können Sie nicht einfach die Wahrheit und die Tatsachen akzeptieren , die Ihnen von einer der autoritativsten Quellen gegeben werden ? !	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'one': [66, 69, 'CARDINAL']}	{}
7672	this page has no references, hence most of the information is not valid	Diese Seite hat keine Referenzen , daher sind die meisten Informationen nicht gültig	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
2670	You're really hot. I watch you when you leave your house. You're very fit, big man.	Sie sind wirklich heiß . Ich beobachtet Sie , wenn Sie Ihr Haus verlassen . Sie sind sehr fit , großer Mann .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
4533	This page is lifted word for word from St. Andrews university web page. Could the author please clarify if they have permission to use it?	Diese Seite ist Wort für Wort von St . Andrews Universität Webseite aufgehoben . Könnte der Autor bitte klären , ob sie die Erlaubnis haben , es zu verwenden ?	[1, 0, 1]	ERR	{'St. Andrews': [39, 50, 'ORG']}	{'Andrews': [39, 46, 'PER']}
6019	Britney Spears discography Continued vandalism will result in having you blocked from Wikipedia.	Britney Spears Diskografie Fortgesetzter Vandalismus wird dazu führen , dass Sie von Wikipedia gesperrt werden .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Britney Spears': [0, 14, 'PERSON'], 'Wikipedia': [86, 95, 'ORG']}	{'Britney Spears': [0, 14, 'PER'], 'Wikipedia': [85, 94, 'MISC']}
7070	You got it wrong. The armed struggle did start in 1973 when the Polisario Front fought against the Spanish, three years before their pullout.	Sie haben es falsch verstanden . Der bewaffnete Kampf begann 1973 , als die Polisario Front gegen die Spanier kämpfte , drei Jahre vor ihrem Ausstieg .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'1973': [50, 54, 'DATE'], 'the Polisario Front': [60, 79, 'ORG'], 'Spanish': [99, 106, 'NORP'], 'three years': [108, 119, 'DATE']}	{'Spanier': [102, 109, 'LOC']}
180	his is your last warning stop violating multiple wikipedia policys and stop being an american retard, do humanity a favour and kill yourself	sein ist Ihre letzte Warnung stoppen Sie mehrere wikipedia - Richtlinien zu verletzen und stoppen Sie , ein amerikanischer retard , tun Sie der Menschheit eine Gunst und töten Sie sich selbst	[1, 0, 1]	ERR	{'wikipedia policys': [49, 66, 'PERSON'], 'american': [85, 93, 'NORP']}	{'amerikanischer': [108, 122, 'MISC']}
6841	One vote to include it either here, or under a subcategories as a online architectural zine.	Eine Stimme , um es entweder hier , oder unter eine Unterkategorie als ein Online - Architektur - Zine .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'One': [0, 3, 'CARDINAL']}	{}
7651	I do remember it being discussed in the early to mid 1980s but not sure exactly when.	Ich erinnere mich , dass es Anfang bis Mitte der 1980er Jahre diskutiert wurde , aber ich weiß nicht genau wann .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'the early to mid 1980s': [36, 58, 'DATE']}	{}
3757	Does it make sense to mention Petit Jean Mountain as a link, seeing as how that just redirects back to Petit Jean State Park?	Ist es sinnvoll , Petit Jean Mountain als Verbindung zu erwähnen , wenn man bedenkt , dass es sich einfach um den Petit Jean State Park dreht ?	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'Petit Jean Mountain': [30, 49, 'PERSON'], 'Petit Jean State Park': [103, 124, 'PERSON']}	{'Petit Jean State Park': [114, 135, 'LOC']}
5394	Jonathan will round house kick Chuck to the face any day of the week. Chuck is secretly a Communist who loves Jesus and Chi Alpha at WSU.	Jonathan wird rund Haus kick Chuck auf das Gesicht jeden Tag der Woche . Chuck ist heimlich ein Kommunist , der Jesus und Chi Alpha am WSU liebt .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'Chuck': [70, 75, 'PERSON'], 'any day of the week': [49, 68, 'DATE'], 'Communist': [90, 99, 'NORP'], 'WSU': [133, 136, 'ORG']}	{'Jonathan': [0, 8, 'LOC'], 'Haus kick Chuck': [19, 34, 'LOC'], 'Tag der Woche': [57, 70, 'MISC'], 'Chuck': [73, 78, 'MISC'], 'Jesus': [112, 117, 'PER'], 'Chi Alpha': [122, 131, 'MISC']}
5782	THIS ARTICLE IS PURE LEFT WING STUPIDITY FROM TOP TO BOTTOM- A WHITEWASH-STALIN RULED BY TERROR-THE MAN WAS A MONSTER	Dieser Artikel ist sicher linkse Flügel Stabilität von oben nach unten - ein WHITEWASH - STALIN von Terror beherrscht - der Mensch war ein Monster	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{'ARTICLE': [5, 12, 'LAW']}	{'WHITEWASH': [77, 86, 'ORG'], 'STALIN': [89, 95, 'MISC'], 'Terror': [100, 106, 'PER']}
5490	Make it permanent, one week is nothing. Don't be afraid.	Machen Sie es permanent , eine Woche ist nichts . Keine Angst .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'one week': [19, 27, 'DATE']}	{}
9427	Dead?== I heard a rumour that Noel is dead. Does anyone know anything about this? ==	Tod ? == Ich hörte einen Gerücht , dass Noel tot ist . Kennt jemand etwas darüber ? ==	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Dead?==': [0, 7, 'ORG'], 'Noel': [30, 34, 'PERSON']}	{'Noel': [40, 44, 'PER']}
1089	All those stupid little blocks will not stop me, I am very patient, I will keep coming back over and over again.	All diese dummen kleinen Blöcke werden mich nicht stoppen , ich bin sehr geduldig , ich werde immer wieder wieder kommen .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
1379	Listen here you son of a bitch. Next time you undo my edits I'm gonna hunt you down and urinate on you. Fuckin Day Walker	Höre hier , du Scheiße . Nächstes Mal , wenn du meine Edits wiederherstellst , werde ich dich jagen und auf dich urinieren .	[3, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'Höre': [0, 4, 'PER']}
6982	Your unblock template below says that the block was imposed by PeterSymonds; I've asked him to examine the situation.	Ihre Entblockungsvorlage unten sagt , dass der Block von PeterSymonds auferlegt wurde ; ich habe ihn gebeten , die Situation zu prüfen .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'PeterSymonds': [57, 69, 'MISC']}
2597	Bbb23, I think you miscounted, because I didn't revert three times. I reverted only once.	Bbb23 , ich denke , du hast falsch gezählt , weil ich nicht dreimal zurückgekehrt bin . Ich habe nur einmal zurückgekehrt .	[0, 1, 1]	ERR	{'three': [55, 60, 'CARDINAL']}	{}
6261	Should it also be mentioned that two of the significant characters, Captain Garth (Heston) and his son were fictional?	Sollte es auch erwähnt werden , dass zwei der bedeutenden Charaktere , Kapitän Garth ( Heston ) und sein Sohn , fiktiv waren ?	[1, 0, 0]	NOT	{'two': [33, 36, 'CARDINAL'], 'Garth': [76, 81, 'PERSON'], 'Heston': [83, 89, 'PERSON']}	{'Garth': [79, 84, 'PER'], 'Heston': [87, 93, 'PER'], 'Sohn': [105, 109, 'PER']}
8746	I can see from the discussion above, that much has been deleted from this article over the years. I wonder if anything good has been slashed.	Ich kann aus der Diskussion oben sehen , dass viel aus diesem Artikel über die Jahre gelöscht wurde . Ich frage mich , ob etwas Gutes abgeschnitten wurde .	[1, 0, 1]	ERR	{'the years': [87, 96, 'DATE']}	{}
7000	"polar bears are completely purple and have scales."""	"Eisbären sind völlig lila und haben Schuppen . """	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
6206	How about some discussion here about the Housemartins' tendencies toward Motown type blue eyed soul?	Wie wäre es mit einer Diskussion hier über die Tendenzen der Housemartins zu Motown - Typ Blue Eyed Soul ?	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Housemartins': [41, 53, 'PERSON'], 'Motown': [73, 79, 'ORG']}	{'Housemartins': [61, 73, 'ORG'], 'Motown': [77, 83, 'ORG']}
9300	I only want people to stop concerning my IP account is not TougHHead and people to stay away from my userpage and my usertalkpage. )	Ich möchte nur , dass Leute aufhören , was mein IP - Konto ist nicht TougHHead und Leute weg von meiner Benutzerseite und meiner Benutzertalkpage zu bleiben . )	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'IP': [41, 43, 'ORG']}	{}
5315	can also use them to make detailed island maps with annotations on.	können sie auch verwenden , um detaillierte Inselkarten mit Anmerkungen auf zu machen .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{}
5826	Disagreeing with your political views does not make someone a racist.	Unzufrieden mit Ihren politischen Ansichten macht jemanden nicht zu einem Rassisten .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
5408	For organization, please list all the latest vandalism warnings, logs, and block notices after this line. Thank you.	Für die Organisation bitte alle neuesten Vandalismuswarnungen , Protokolle und Block - Bemerkungen nach dieser Zeile auflisten . Vielen Dank .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{'Vielen Dank': [129, 140, 'PER']}
3566	Removed Redirect I removed the redirect of the Sinless perfection page to Christian perfection as it was a term that early Methodist didn't use.	Entfernt Umleitung Ich habe die Umleitung der Sündelosen Perfektion Seite zur christlichen Perfektion entfernt , da es ein Begriff war , den der frühe Methodist nicht benutzte .	[1, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Christian': [74, 83, 'NORP'], 'Methodist': [123, 132, 'ORG']}	{'christlichen': [78, 90, 'MISC']}
362	I really enjoy licking penis. I routinely check into hotles with she-males in order to get rammed by them also. After all, my name is uncle dick.	Ich genieße wirklich lecken Penis . Ich routinemäßig in Hotles mit she - Männern überprüfen , um von ihnen auch geschlagen zu bekommen . Schließlich ist mein Name Onkel dick .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'Ich genieße wirklich lecken Penis': [0, 33, 'MISC'], 'Hotles': [56, 62, 'LOC']}
4768	If you visited Middlesbrough especially the riverside stadium you would understand why they are called the smoggies. The air is like a thick sut )	Wenn Sie Middlesbrough besucht haben , vor allem das Riverside - Stadion , würden Sie verstehen , warum sie die Smoggies genannt werden . Die Luft ist wie eine dicke Sut )	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Middlesbrough': [15, 28, 'GPE']}	{'Middlesbrough': [9, 22, 'LOC'], 'Riverside': [53, 62, 'LOC']}
8387	Ok and also I wasnt removing the one link and replacing it. I was just adding the other link. If i was removing the one it was a mistake.	Ok und auch war ich nicht entfernen die eine Verbindung und ersetzen es . Ich war nur hinzufügen der anderen Verbindung . Wenn ich die eine entfernte es war ein Fehler .	[1, 1, 1]	ERR	{}	{'Ok': [0, 2, 'MISC']}
9383	The article's mention makes it sound as if it was slavery.	Die Erwähnung des Artikels macht es so klingen , als ob es eine Sklaverei war .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{}	{}
3950	Question Wondering why you removed referenced content from the article Sam Harper.	Frage Sie fragen sich , warum Sie referenzielle Inhalte aus dem Artikel Sam Harper entfernt haben .	[1, 0, 1]	ERR	{'Sam Harper': [71, 81, 'PERSON']}	{'Sam Harper': [72, 82, 'PER']}
720	There is NO evidence to sustansiate this claim, will you please delete it. Renée.	Es gibt KEINE Beweise , um diese Behauptung zu rechtfertigen , würden Sie es bitte löschen . Renée .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'Renée': [75, 80, 'PERSON']}	{'Renée': [93, 98, 'PER']}
1186	Adding advertisements to wikipedia articles is a bad idea, as they will just be removed.	Das Hinzufügen von Anzeigen zu wikipedia - Artikeln ist eine schlechte Idee , da sie einfach entfernt werden .	[0, 0, 0]	NOT	{'wikipedia': [25, 34, 'ORG']}	{'wikipedia': [31, 40, 'MISC']}
